Go! Go!
Yo, Jimmy, man,
give me the status.
Tell me we good.
We got it, man.
Beautiful.
It's gonna be
an all-timer tonight.
All right,
all right, all right.
Fire 'em up!
We go live in five.
It's time for ignition
and straight automobile pimp.
Let's do it, man.
Let's go.
Ow, girl!
Sorry! My bad!
All right, ladies!
We're good!
We're good.
That's it, babies.
Come on, Tej.
Let's get this race going!
Whoa, whoa, man.
Wait a second, man.
You cats are first wave, man.
Where's your fourth at?
Yo, it was Joaquin, but he had
to work the graveyard shift.
What?
Graveyard shift, man?
Yo, why don't you
run with us, Tej?
Hell, no, I'm not runnin'
with y'all, man.
Either you find a fourth
or you don't race.
- How 'bout that, huh?
- We should find two...
so we don't have to roll
with skirt here.
Oooh!
Idiota.
Whoa. Whoa.
Wait a second.
Why don't I just find y'all
a fourth and we settle
this on the streets, huh?
- Bring him on.
- Anybody I want?
- No matter who it is.
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
You wanna race tonight?
- Yeah. You know
I could use the money.
- You got four minutes.
- All right. I'll be there.
The race starts
in four minutes.
All right, girls.
Let's do this.
*2 furious
I'm too fast for y'all, man *
*Drah, 2 fast
Drah, 2 furious *
*I'm too fast
for y'all, man *
You think
you gonna win baby?
What you think?
You better.
We got rent to pay.
I know this.
* You just came home
from doin'a bid *
* Tell me what ya gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Somebody broke in
and cleaned out your crib *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Man, that ain't sticky
That's sticks and stems *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*2 fast, 2 fast
2 furious, 2 furious **
I'll get you when
you get a car worth racing.
Yeah. There's
our fourth right there.
- Shit. It's Brian.
Yeah, Brian.!
I love you, Bullet.!
What's up, Tej?
What's happenin', dude?
Thanks for the invite.
No problem at all, man.
Just, uh...
Just remember me
when you wax, right?
They got deep pockets?
Real deep.
- What's up, Suki?
- What's up, Bullet?
- What do you say
we kick it a nickel?
Nobody said nothin'
about raisin' the stakes.
If that's the case,
why don't you ask
these nice people here...
to back off the line
so you can go home?
Oooh.!
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Okay. Thirty-five large.
Three cinco.
Thirty-five large, huh?
Either that or you
can go home, brah.
Yeah.
- It's all there.
- It better be.
Damn, Suki.
Uh, when you gonna
pop my clutch, huh?
As soon as you
get the right
set of tools.
Yeah, right.
All right, back up.
Back up. Let's go. Let's go.
Whoa!
Back y'all asses up.
Back up. Back up.
Before you turn
into barbecue around here.
It's not a game.
This is serious.
All right. Back up. Back up.
Get off the street.
Let's go. Back it up.
Back it up.
Everybody keep your hands
real, real clear, all right?
'Cause I got a surprise
for y'all this evening.
Go, SlapJack!
Go, baby!
I got this. I got this.
Ready.
Go!
- Oh, hell, no!
Aaah!
Aha!
You ain't passin' me, dawg.
You ain't passin' me. Come on!
What you got, man?
I told you
you weren't gonna pass me.
- Move, bitch!
- Ha!
Pendeja.!
Uh-uh. Not tonight, baby.
Bend over, boy.
Damn, girl!
Last turn. Last turn.
Oh, too wide!
Home stretch, baby!
Whoo-h-h-hoo!
Let it go, dawg!
Yes!
I can smell you!
Yo, Jimmy,
hit it, baby. Hit it!
Right. Y'all see that?
Told y'all
I had a surprise.
How you like that
for a finale?
Bridge.
- Oh!
- Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Shit!
Huh? Oh, hell, no!
Whoo! Smack that ass!
Yes!
Tell me y'all saw that, man.
Bullet and Suki sprayed
the bridge,
and I need to start
making y'all pay
to see this shit.
I got over 10 stacks
for my man right here, right?
That's what
I'm talkin' about, man.
Play with it.
Smells good, don't it?
Yeah, I'll buy that.
Right there.
Right. Y'all see this?
Everybody take
a real good look.
This what you call
mutual respect.
Right, let's clear out.
Anybody down
for another race?
Shit!
Hey, uh, make sure
you bring that body
by the garage later, right,
so, you know,
we can work on
that front end of yours.
Watch out.
'Cause maybe I will.
Yeah.
What's up, man?
Hey, where you going?
It's time
to get out of here.
Why's that?
Oh, shit!
Nissan Skyline. Got him.
Shit! Shit!
Shit...
Shit.
Damn!
Let me see your hands!
Put 'em up!
This is him. We got him.!
So, how long you been
in south Florida?
A while.
Before that?
We know you're
Brian O'Conner,
formerly of the L.A.P.D.
- You've got the wrong guy.
- Really?
How you doin, O'Conner?
Let's take a walk.
Carter Verone.
Born in Argentina.
But he's lived
most of his life in Miami.
Now he owns
the biggest import/ export
business in the state.
Unfortunately, the cartels
have been successful
getting drugs into Miami.
But they've had
a hard time gettin'
the cash out.
We've been
surveilling him for a year,
but we've never been able...
to put him
and the money together.
- We've swept his house,
his warehouses...
- Nothing.
Customs here has done
a great job of getting us
this far.
I'm just here to help get
them over the top.
I was able to get
an agent in undercover...
working travel
and logistics for him.
Recently, Verone put her
in charge of finding
some new drivers.
Right. Although we can't
confirm her status right now.
You think she's flipped?
She's one of mine.
She's all right.
She's been in with Verone
nearly a year. Even lives
at the compound with him now.
Look, it was the F.B.I.'s idea
to bring you in here.
I'm against it. But we need
some good drivers...
that can put this asshole
and his money together.
You're gonna roll
with Agent Dunn here.
And if I don't?
Well, here's a list
of the laws you broke in L.A.
Obstruction of justice,
aiding and abetting.
You know the rap sheet.
Now, we can make this
all go away in the interest
of justice,
if you're willing
to play ball.
Yeah.
So what's the idea here?
Dunn and I are supposed
to be street racers?
That's right.
So, Dunn...
Looks like we're gonna
be partners, bro.
Could you tell me right quick
what would be a better motor
for my Skyline,
a Gallo 12 or a Gallo 24?
Um...
The 24.
I didn't know
pizza places made motors.
See, man, come on.
I can't do this.
Seriously,
if this is what
you're gonna give me,
I may as well
take my chances in Chino.
We will
get someone else.
No way, man.
The only way I'll do this is
if I get to pick the driver.
All right, O'Conner,
who you got in mind?
This dude I grew up with
in Barstow.
Who's that?
Roman Pearce.
Hi-oh! What...
- That's your boy
in the Monte Carlo?
- Yeah, that's him.
Yeah, he's got some skills.
Mm-hmm.
And he's crazy as hell,
I'm telling ya.
In a good way though.
He's the man for the job.
He's got quite a record,
including three years upstate.
Says here he's on
house arrest now. Can't go more
than 100 yards from his home.
Roman Pearce.!
Whoo-hoo.!
He always said
he'd be famous.
Pearce.!
Roman Pearce!
- Yo, whatever happens next,
just let it go.
- I ain't in it.
Rome!
Only my homeboys
call me Rome, pig!
- I'm not a cop anymore, bro.
- Is that true?
- Blondie here's
not a cop anymore?
- That's true. No badge.
Whoo! Here we go.
You still fight like shit.
You still fight like shit...
You better chill.
What the hell
are you doin' here, O'Conner?
I'll choke you.
I told you
to stay away from...
You should've told me.
I did three years, Brian.
I told you
it wasn't my fault.
Why did you
come here, O'Conner?
I got a deal for you.
When I needed your ass,
you were nowhere to be found.
Now you tryin'
to hand out deals?
I need you
to come to Miami
and drive with me.
If you do, they'll take off
that anklet and they'll
clear your entire record.
I did three years in jail.
Three years in jail
off you, Brian.
I know you better
than you think.
Maybe you don't.
You guys finished?
This deal legit?
That's right, if you
do this job for us.
Told you.
Shut up, punk.
So you gonna clean
my record and get this
thing off my ankle?
That's right. I thought you
couldn't wander more than
100 yards from your home.
Why do you think
I'm parked so close
to the derby?
Man, quit playin' like
you gonna pass this up.
Wait. Hold up.
Hey, bro,
what's going on?
I don't know
if I should be
trusting you, man.
Just think of it this way.
It's an opportunity
for a fresh start.
Let's just go do this.
I wouldn't need
a fresh start...
if it weren't for you.
Man, you been using that
since the day you got busted.
Now, let's just chill out
and go do this.
I don't need to chill out.
Yes, you do. And you
need to stop blaming me
for your every mistake.
And Roman Pearce needs
to start taking responsibility
for his own actions.
You need to go to hell.
And you need
to go back to Barstow.
I'm not goin'
back to Barstow.
Brian O'Conner,
Roman Pearce,
meet Monica Fuentes.
- Do they have
background on Verone?
- They've been briefed.
Good. All right,
here's the deal.
Verone's looking for drivers.
I've arranged for
both of you to join up.
I've also hired some thugs.
You know, to make it legit.
- When do we start?
- Right now.
- What are we drivin'?
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Don't even think about
takin' the convertible.
It might
loosen your mousse.
No, that's cool.
That's too much
chrome for me anyways.
Damn! Where you all confiscate
these rims from, man?
Check in with us
after you meet him.
You gonna have any problems
with these two knuckleheads?
I can handle 'em.
They give you any trouble
at all, you let me know.
Thanks, Markham.
I'll ride with you,
cowboy.
Why she gotta ride with you.
You get the convertible.
Let's go.
* That's where I reside *
* That's where I'll represent
till I die *
*So get changed
and put your drinks down *
*And get sexed up
and get wowed for tonight *
*Pit bull like a sex bull
like the next truck
Mama, you got the next *
Turn right here.
So you used to be a cop?
Yeah.
How long you been under?
I lost track.
You all right?
You might wanna keep
your eyes on the road, playboy.
What, you think
we're gonna crash?
I haven't decided yet.
What are you doin', Brian?
He did the "stare and drive"
on you, didn't he?
He got that from me.
*Represent your county
your city *
* Who you know
pull Chevys like this *
* Can't he pace with a trunk
in a funk like this *
* With the loose top *
*And the rims keep spinnin'
even when I stop *
*Murder one, I'll be chillin'
Got everybody watchin'
but who gonna stop me *
* The first game, soda *
*Somebody tries some mo'shit
buys some mo'shit *
*I "T"doubled 'em
switched the game *
* Got next slope down
switchin'lanes *
* Chevy boys, we like it fast
so I drop it in low
heavy on the gas **
Once we get in here,
you're on your own.
Look at that one.
Hey, where did you
get them cars, the bottom
of a cereal box?
Eh! Real funny, Fonzie.
Ass.
Roberto, Enrique,
I need pictures of
the drivers,
their license plates,
their cars, and anything else
you can find.
Let's go.
Keep your mouth shut
and follow my lead, all right?
I got this.
No, I'm serious now.
Handle your business.
I'll handle mine.
Watch your hands, brah.
Go in line.
Let's go.
Carter.
Drivers are here.
Good.
Come on.
Stay.
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
My red Ferrari was confiscated
yesterday, and it sits in
an impound lot in Little Haiti.
It's about
20 miles from here.
The car isn't important.
What is important is the package
I left in the glove box.
The first team back here
with the package will have
an opportunity to work for me.
- What, we gotta audition?
- Nobody's got a gun
to your head.
That's it.
Driver's licenses.
Pass 'em up.
Before Christmas, guys.
Go!
Go! Go, man.
Come on. Go!
Come on, cuz.
All right,
let's see what
this thing can do.
Agent Markham,
I've got 'em
heading south on l-95.
Yeah, I got it.
They're running.
What a surprise.
Come on. Stick with me, Rome.
What you got?
Why must I chase the cat?
Smart ass.
- Oh, yeah? You think
you're the bomb, Rome?
Let's see if
you still got it, Brian.
All right, Rome.
I got somethin'
for your ass.
Watch this, bro.
Shit.
Yeah, Rome.
How do you like
them apples?
Show off!
That's the Brian O'Conner
school of driving
right there, baby.
Crazy-ass white boy!
Oh, shit!
- Hey, man.
- Huh?
Get yourself on
outta the street.!
Boy, that's some
bad shit, man.
What do we got?
That's good.
Show me his partner.
Cars. Cars.
Where are the cars?
Stinkin' boats.
I need the cars.
Where are the cars at?
Look in the center.
What?
Chi-ching! Now put
your blouse back on.
Hater.
Shit.!
- Don't let 'em get away.
- Not a problem.
Sit on it, Fonzie!
- What the hell?
Aw, shit! Cops.
- What the hell
they doin' here?
- Rome, no.!
Time to go.
- Son of a bitch!
Juvie record for popping cars.
Two years in J.D.,
then another year for aiding
and abetting an armed robbery.
He's clean.
Dirty but clean.
Hm. All right.
Hey, man, you got
somethin'to eat
up in there? We hungry.
Sit 'em by the pool.
Mm-hmm.
Nice. Come on.
Hmm.
What you checking
her out for?
I'm not
checking her out.
Yes, you were.
No, I wasn't.
I seen you
checkin' her out, man.
Okay, I was. Now shut up.
You shut up.
Don't tell me to shut up.
Both you girlies
shut up.
Unbelievable.
All right.
You sure are cozy
in this big ol' mansion.
Sleepin' with
the enemy.
No, no, no.
Sit down.
Nice Ferrari
you got in the driveway.
I'm glad you like it.
Darlin',
will you hold that?
We did all that
for a damn cigar?
No, you did that
for a job.
Do you really think
that I would let
somebody impound my car?
The boatyard's mine.
Oh, by the way,
you two owe me a gate.
- But I'll just
take it off your cut.
Off our cut. Yeah.
- I like that.
- Good.
What's this job
you got for us anyway?
Come with me.
The house has ears in it.
I have something I want you
to carry from North Beach
to the Keys.
What is it?
Just put in the car
what I tell you to,
drive it to me
and don't let anyone
stop you, understand?
Yeah. Any chance
of cop trouble?
No. I'm buying you
a window of time, but it's
not gonna be open very long.
You make it,
and I'll personally hand you
100 G's at the finish line.
Make it 100 G's
a piece, papi.
Look, man, obviously,
your pockets
ain't nervous.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't ever touch me.
Ours are empty.
Like I said,
we hungry.
I got an idea.
Why don't you two boys
join us at the club
a little later tonight?
- Yeah. Pearl at midnight?
- We'll get to know
each other a little better.
All right.
Sounds good.
We'll see you tonight.
See ya.
Hey, you!
Your pockets aren't empty.
- Damn.
- I'll take my cutter back.
Stupid ass.
Hey, man,
I figured you
had, like, 12 or 13...
You're not too bright,
are you?
Just get out of here.
Same old Rome
doin' the same old
stupid shit.
Get off me, man.
What, runnin' your mouth?
Insultin' people?
Stealin' Verone's shit?
Think I'm gonna let
somebody stare me down?
I didn't let nobody
stare me down in jail,
homeboy.
Think I'm gonna
let it fly on a beach?
And you, I'll take
my cutter back.
His rich ass.
And you're packin'!
Like you ain't?
Exactly.
- From here, I do the talkin'.
- Looks like you wanna do
a little more than that.
Oh, and what's that
supposed to mean?
It means you always
gettin' in trouble
over a female, Brian.
Man, Tej's garage is ridiculous.
He's got the best of everything.
Snap-on tools. All these lifts
are brand-new. They're only
maybe a couple months old.
Hey, yo, Jimmy.
What's up, man?
What up, Bullet?
That's Rome right there.
When you get a second,
I want you to check out...
the Evo and the Spyder
and make sure
everything's copecetic.
Evo? Where'd you get
an Evo from?
Well, it's
a long story.
I got you, man.
All right,
thanks, Jimmy.
Come check this out.
It's so hot and humid
out here, I can't even
wear no drawers.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Look at all
this potential out here.
Don't do that, man.
Damn!
Damn. Baby.
Girl, you know
your boy can help
you put that fire out.
Look at the bubble
on that...
That's cool.
That's serious right there.
You're making me lose money.
Don't do that to me right now.
I cannot take that right...
Come on, Ray! Do it!
Hey, Tej Parker,
Roman Pearce.
Come on, baby...
Basically, he's the man
to know in Miami.
He's got his finger
in absolutely everything.
It's just
the way it is.
What's goin' on, Suki?
What's up, baby?
How you doing?
I'm good.
What's this?
What's the latest?
It's a work in progress.
It's not finished yet.
That's some artistic shit.
You got talent, girl.
Yeah, she's good.
She's the best.
Do or die. Bring it home, Ray.
Bring it home, Ray.
Bring it home. Bring it home.
Yeah, baby! Pay up!
Pay up! Pay up!
That's how they
do it out here, man?
Every day.
That's crazy.
Right here, right now.
What's up, man?
You don't look too happy.
Right? Expeditiously, man.
I need it quick right here.
What's up?
Thank you.
Thank you. All right.
How you feeling? Right?
Right.
Thank you.
Thank you, man.
Not too bad.
Whoo!
I'll see you
about your money, homey.
You race too?
No, man.
I hit a wall doin',
like, a buck 20
couple years ago, you know?
Ever since then,
I just been organizing
and collecting, man.
Tej, check it out.
He's gonna be in town
for a while.
Is there anyway
he could use that cot?
What's wrong
with your place, man?
No, I don't
wanna stay with him.
He got bad habits.
right, man.
Whatever, man.
Show him around
real quick, right?
I'll be up there in a minute.
Thanks.
right, who want a chance
to win their money back?
What's up, Jimmy?
So you ever seen
anything like this before?
No. Both of them
are wired up
like I never seen before.
What?
Yeah, man. They got us
wired with G.P.S.
That's why Markham
knew we were gonna be
at that impound lot.
Yo, you the master mechanic.
Why don't you just yank
that shit up out of there?
I'll try, but
this ain't LoJack.
The D.I.S. Box,
the engine management system,
hell, the main harness...
The G.P.S. Is spidered
into all of that.
Hey, tell me somethin', man.
Do I even want to know
where the Skyline is, dawg?
Or where you been
the past couple of days?
Or where the hell
you got these rides from?
They're hot.
Yeah, they hot. They wired
so hot that whoever's trackin'
these things will know...
every time you don't
wear your seat belt.
All right, Jimmy,
just do what
you can do, bro.
- I got ya.
- Thanks, man.
Man, we need to get
these on the street ASAP.
Hey, bro,
check it out.
You see that Cadillac
across the street
over there?
Yeah.
Yeah, well, they've been on us
since we left Verone's house.
Elian and Fidel!
Hey, man, I'll clean
your windshield for you.
- What are you doin', man?
Uno, tres, cuatro,
"fourtro," taco.
Everything's copecetic, homey.
Kiss my ass, putos.
Shit!
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
He's gonna blow our cover
before we even get started.
Hey, Bilkins, can you
tell me what went wrong?
That's what I wanna know.
Show me your hands!
Come on. Keep 'em up!
- What's this about, man?
- Hey, w-what's goin' on?
Hold this.
You think you can shoot at me?
I'm a goddamn federal agent!
What are you talkin' about?
Get your damn hands off me!
Get him away from me!
Just 'cause you wear a badge
don't mean you can come in
and mess shit up.!
- Get your hands off of me!
- You're lucky
I didn't shoot you.
- Shut up, Rome!
- Don't tell me
to shut up, Brian!
You almost blew our cover,
old man.
You shouldn't have
shown up like you did.
What, you didn't know
Verone was testing us?
- No. I thought you punks
were running.
- Running!
That's great.
That's real great!
Oh, and if Rome wanted
to shoot you, you wouldn't
be here right now.
All right.
We gotta get this
under control.
Hey, that's mine.!
- So?
- So tell me what you know.
Well, Rome and I will be
making a run for Verone.
I'm not sure when and where.
But he did say
he bought us a window.
I'm assuming
from the local cops.
I can talk to
some of the guys
at the local P.D.
No. No good. If Verone's got
some of them on the payroll,
then we can't let them know
our operation.
Exactly. In addition,
Verone told us that he himself
would be waiting at the drop.
That's good news.
If you're gonna be
delivering drug money to him,
- then we can get him
for laundering.
- No, there's only one problem.
- What's that?
- Fuentes...
Verone's tappin' her.
Tappin' her?
Tappin' her how?
That is crap!
What you talkin' about,
homeboy? We know what we seen.
What do you think, O'Conner?
You think she's compromised?
- You should know.
- What's that supposed to mean?
What? You mean your old pal
O'Conner didn't tell ya?
He flipped on Bilkins in L.A.
Gave his mark his car keys
and let him disappear.
That's why he's not
a cop anymore.
So what do you think, expert?
Man, I don't know.
All right.
We'll keep an eye on her.
We're out of here.
You let your man go, huh?
Drop it. I don't
wanna talk about it.
Drop it, hell!
I wanna hear
about this, homey.
I said forget about it, cuz.
We got Fuentes in with Verone,
Markham tryin'
to blow our cover...
and we got two wired cars
that are no better than that
damn ankle bracelet of mine.
I'm-a tell you, brah.
You let your man Markham do that
shit again in front of Verone,
- that's gonna be our ass.
- I know, man. I know.
It's gettin' thick real quick,
and we may need a way out.
- We gotta come up with
some exit strategy.
- Exit strategy, huh?
Yeah.
I like the way that sounds.
What you got in mind?
I don't know, man.
But we need two more cars.
Yeah. Here they come.
Fonzie and Fabio.
Glad you can join us.
We heard you boys
wanted to get rid
of those CrackerJack toys.
No. Actually we just figured
those cars you got
deserved better drivers,
which is why we're gonna
take 'em off your hands.
- You know, why don't
we settle this now?
- Wait, wait.
How about we settle this
on the blacktop, huh?
Each car does it
down and back,
tag-team style...
for slips.
Loser walks home.
- We came to race.
- Well, load 'em up then.
Come on, bro.
Let's get these cars.
All right, check it out.
There's no way we gonna beat
these guys straight up.
The Hemi's puttin' out
about 425...
and that Yenko
will snap a speed on
about five seconds flat.
We're gonna have to pull
somethin' out of our ass.
The only thing I can think of
is save the spray for
the way back, the return trip.
Done deal.
All right.
Let's do this, bro.
I'm gettin'
that orange one.
You ain't ready, Fabio!
All right. You each
got a barrel to go around
down at the end of the road.
The second wave gotta
sit tight till your partner
crosses this line right here.
First team to go
down and back twice
wins the race.
At which point,
the losers will
hand over them keys.
Otherwise, you'll be eatin'
breakfast through straws
from now on.
Comprende?
I get it.
Oh, this means you too.
- I got it.
- right.
Let's race.
Come on, baby.!
You got this, Rome.
Let's do it.
Hey, you gone, homey.
I got this. This is done.
You about to lose
your car.
Do it, Rome!
Come on.
You got it.
You think I'm worried
about this fool, man?
This is nothin'.
- Aw, no.
- American muscle.
Your engine ain't
as big as your mouth.
Gotta smoke 'em. Gotta
smoke 'em. Gotta smoke 'em.
All right, here we go.
It's all right, baby.
I'm gonna handle this.
Handle it.
Ready and... go!
You ain't ready.
I run these streets.
Woo-hoo!
Romey Rome.
You ain't heard of me?
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah!
I'm-a get you.
Oh, I'm-a get you!
Where's your
big mouth now, boy?
That car's going home
with me, homey.
Oh, shit.
Eat this, sucker!
Shit!
Yeah, boy!
Go, Korpi!
Sorry, blondie.
How does that dust taste?
I don't know.
Come on, Rome.
What the...
Good move, kid. Let's see
if you got the balls. Come on!
- Whoo!
Goddamn! Come on!
Come on, Brian.
Bring it home, man.
Got two new cars!
That's all my man!
- Damn!
Y'all ain't ready, homeboy.
Get to walkin', Fabio.
Use them bus tokens, partner.!
Hey, how you doin'?
Good. What you need?
We're guests
of Mr. Verone's.
- It's a "hoasis"
in here, brah.
- Yeah.
Lots of potential.
Damn. You got a pen?
Phew. It's about to
get serious, brah.
Look at that girl
on the swing right there.
Hey. You guys
did something right.
- Verone never socializes
with hired help.
- Then what's that make you?
- Where's he at?
- He's on his way.
- You and Verone don't go
everywhere together?
- What's that supposed to mean?
Nothin'.
Huh. I'm-a go
take a piss.
You go do that.
What is his deal?
He doesn't trust people
that carry badges.
So you talk
like you know.
Yeah.
I'd been a cop
about two months...
when Roman was busted
in a garage raid.
He had eight sets of wheels
in his possession, each
and every one of them hot.
So you busted him?
No. I didn't even know
what was goin' down.
But, uh, that doesn't
really matter to him.
Basically, once
I became a cop,
Roman started
seeing me as a friend
that became the enemy.
You have a little...
Is there anything
I can get for you,
Mr. Verone?
Just tell 'em
to comejoin me.
Oh, yeah.
I was admiring this.
Yeah, I was looking
at it earlier.
- Damn.
- I wasn't about
to give it to you.
What's up?
He's here, man.
Where's he at?
He's over there.
Don't look.
Excuse me.
Mr. Verone would like
for you to join him.
Let's do it.
See what I'm talkin' about?
It's all right.
Let 'em in.
Go sit down.
I'll talk to you
in a second.
How ya doin'?
Good. You enjoying
your night?
Yeah. I'm havin'
a good time.
Good, good.
She's beautiful,
isn't she?
Hmm?
Yeah.
She's gorgeous.
You got balls, kid.
I can appreciate that.
Women are a very
powerful force.
You see the blond
sitting with
the gentleman right here?
Five minutes of her time,
and she can get anything
she wants from him.
- I love your hair.
- Watch.
I wonder where
they're going.
Sit down.
So, you, uh, lit my man's
car on fire. Is that right?
Yeah. I did.
You see, I got a problem
with authority.
Hmm. I have
that same problem.
For me, it's cops
in particular.
Let's take a walk.
Come on.
We just got here.
Now we're leaving.
Let's go.
Hey. Come on.
What's all that?
We're gonna have
a little fun.
- Hmm.
Thank you.
Let's just stay
a little longer.
- Hey, Carter.
Meet, uh,
Detective Whitworth.
One of Miami's finest.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Are you enjoying
yourself, Detective?
Yeah. I was.
I mean, you know me.
Yeah, I do know you.
- You been on my payroll
a long time.
- Verone, that ain't right.
Shut up.
I got one last job
for you, Detective.
You hear me?
Look, we've been
all through this.
Yeah?
Yeah. I said
I can't do it.
Hmm. That's
the wrong answer.
The table.
I'm a detective, Verone!
You do anything to me,
the whole force is gonna
be on your ass
in a minute.
Shut your mouth!
You fat piece of shit.
You can stop right now.
- What the hell...
What the hell is that?
- Sit down.
You're gonna regret this.
Just stop right now!
Once the bucket
gets hot enough,
Detective,
the rat is gonna
want out.
Get...
And the only direction
it can go is south.
Hey! Get...
Hey!
Hold that.
- Get it off me!
I'll forget it ever happened.
- Shut up.
Did you know that
your average rat...
Can chew through
a steel drain pipe?
You see, you have nothing
to worry about when he's
screaming, Detective.
It's when he goes quiet
that he goes to work.
Stop it.! Stop it.!
Stop it.!
Don't be stupid.
Stop it now.
You're in charge of the units
that are watching
my properties, huh?
What I want is,
I want a 15-minute window...
where everybody...
and I mean everybody...
disappears.
You hear me?
I can't do it!
- Stop it.
I can't do it. Help.!
- Okay. Monica, come here.
- Help.! Help.!
- Shut him up.
Shut him up.
Help! Help!
Help.!
He's biting me!
- Help.! Help.!
- What?
- You got somethin'
you wanna say?
He bit me!
- Yes, I'll do it.!
- Do what? Say it.
I'll do it.
I'll give you your window.
Just get it off me!
Get it off!
You betray me,
and my rat here...
is gonna visit
your wife, Lynn... yeah...
your son, Clay,
and your daughter, Lexi.
Do you hear me?
You understand me? Huh?
You hear me?
Yes.
I'll burn your... eyes out!
I'll burn 'em out!
Get it off me.
Good. Now you can go.
Get rid ofhim.
Let's go.
Get if off!
Mm. You boys
enjoy the show?
Fifteen minutes, and then
every cop in Florida
is gonna be on you.
Be at Versailles Cafe,
6:00 a.m., day after tomorrow,
ready to drive.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
Don't play games with me,
or you'll be next. All right?
Help yourself
to a little champagne.
Let's go.
That was
a damn rat, man.
Hey.
You ever... touch
another man again,
and I'll kill you.
You hear me?
Look at me.
She was into it, man.
What's that about?
And you seen the way
she grabbed
the dude's head.
She had to, man.
He was testing her.
You gotta remember,
her ass is on the line,
just like ours.
You feelin' this girl
way too much.
She just like that
crazy-ass trailer-raff
from back-in-the-day, Tonya.
Tonya? Man, you
went out with her
after I did.
I mean, I couldn't
let her go to waste.
I got you, I got you,
I got you.
Is that right?
See, we can race
for cash,
but when I step on the gas,
my nitrous go blast,
leave your ass in the past.
And, Tej, you about
to lose your garage.
Whatever, man.
I'm a low-budget mechanic,
but I overcharge.
Pay me!
Let's go, man!
Pay me my money.
I told you, man.
You a happy man.
I'm so glad.
This is my garage, boy.
Royal flush!
Give me this, man.
Holler, huh! Yes!
Did I talk to him?
Talk to him.
Damn.
You can't play a player. Put
that money back on the table.
You know it's my next hand.
Jimmy, how you
gonna pay me back
if you keep losing to Tej?
How ya doin', bro?
I'm gonna crash, Tej.
I'll catch you tomorrow.
right, boy.
- What are you doin' here?
- Brian, they're gonna
kill you.
I heard him telling
Enrique and Roberto.
Once you finish the run, they're
putting a bullet in your head.
- You sure
you heard 'em right?
- I'm sure. I'm sure.
- Verone's boys is outs...
Oh, I see what
they lookin'for...
your little girlfriend here.
- They don't know I'm here.
I snuck out.
- What are they doin' here then?
I don't know.
Maybe they're guessing.
Hey, go stall them.
- Go stall them
for two minutes.
- Check her, homey. Check her.
Find what you was
lookin' for?
Hey, buddy. Hi, guys.
How ya doin'?
Oh, man, y'all still mad
about y'all car?
Don't even trip, homey.
Come on, man.
You can't take a joke?
Brian, this isn't about
being a good cop anymore
or-or doing your job.
They're gonna kill you.
You guys gotta pull out.
Verone pay y'all to keep
a straight face like that?
'Cause if I was makin'money,
shit, I'd get that mole
removed off my damn nose.
Okay? Okay.
Yeah.
How much
he pay y'all anyway?
Every time I see y'all, man,
y'all got the silk shirts on,
jewelry, you know,
lookin'real Miami.
You know? I caught you
walkin' up in the club,
you got the hamburger meat
all hangin' out, you know?
Don't make that run, Brian.
Don't make that run.
Be careful.
- Donde esta?
- Quien?
- You ain't comin' on my...
Hey, hey! Where you goin'?
You stay right here
with us, buddy.
Don't even think
about it.
Vamonos.!
Stay your ass off
my homeboy's boat.
Put the gun down!
Put the gun down now!
You first, asshole!
You first!
I'll shoot the shit
outta him!
Put the gun down!
- Tu primero.!
- Put down the gun now!
- Put down the gun!
Enough.
- Enough. Shut up.
Shut up.
It's over. Come on.
It's over. Let's go.
Let's have the gun. Come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
I'm glad to see you boys
are getting along so well.
Because tomorrow,
Roberto and Enrique...
are gonna be
riding along with you...
just so that we don't
have any problems.
I'll see you guys
in a bit.
What the hell was she
doin' in there, man?
Where'd you go
this morning?
I went to breakfast
with some friends.
- With friends.
I do have friends, Carter.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
- Nice shirt, Bilkins.
- It's my day off.
Yeah. Well, anyhow,
this is the deal.
Last night,
Verone threatened a cop
into giving us a window.
We're driving to an airstrip,
in the Keys,
off of Nallwood Avenue.
Verone has a plane there,
and he's taking off
for good.
- Wait a minute.
How do you know this?
- Monica.
She's doin' her job.
She warned us.
- She warned you about what?
- Verone plans to kill us
after we give him the money.
Driving into an ambush
was never part of the deal.
I'm calling this off.
Like hell you are. This
is a Customs case, Bilkins.
No one's calling this off
unless I do.
Look. This is real simple.
You make the run.
You get Verone
and his cash together...
so I can move in
for the bust.
All right? You don't, I will
find enough charges on both
of you to make you disappear.
Take these. We're gonna
have G.P.S. On you
the whole time...
to make sure you don't
get any cute ideas.
- And to make sure nothing
happens to them, right?
- Yeah, right.
The guy's a dick, man.
Yep.
Let me get this right.
If we don't do this,
then we go to jail.
But if we do it, then
Verone's gonna kill us.
It's a hell of a deal,
huh?
Yeah. Maybe it is.
But I know this guy's
got an ass full of loot...
that he's ready
to dump in our cars.
And I can think of two reasons
why Verone doesn't need
that money anymore.
- Ah, here we go.
- You and me.
Just like the old days.
What do you think?
I think they messed with
the wrong two guys.
That's what I think.
Yo, Tej.
What's up, bro?
What up?
Hey, man, how quickly
can you organize?
Look, folk,
if y'all really wanna
carry out this plan,
it's definitely
the best place to do it.
What do y'all think, man?
I think it's perfect.
What do they store here?
*Pump, p-p-pump, pump
P-P-P-Pump *
*Pump, p-p-pump
Pump it up *
Pump, p-pump, p-pump *
Hey, man, this thing's clean.
*Pump it up
Just blaze *
Strip it down.
*Pump, p-p-pump, pump it up *
* We gonna do it like
uh, uh, uh *
*Look, pump it up if you came
to get it krunk with a dame
and shit that's drunk *
* You came to get it on
More than five O's
in your bank *
* Then get it on
Roll up like that stank
and get it on *
*Slank that fitted on
Came to get it on *
Hey, Jimmy.
Yeah. What up?
We have any half-empty bottles
of nitrous laying around?
Sure, but I already
loaded you for spray.
No. I'm thinkin'
we may need it
for somethin' else,
'cause our cars may get
a little crowded,
you know?
*Pump, p-p-pump
Pump it up **
Man, when you start
eatin' so much?
I was in jail, brah.
I know how shitty
the grub is
on the inside.
With the way things is shapin'
up out here right now,
it'll be a matter of time
before I'm back in there
or dead.
So I'm tryin' to eat
all I can while I can.
Plus the doctor tell me
I got a high metabolism.
Man, you remember us
growing up?
You know, playing
football in the dirt.
You know, gettin' in trouble,
all the stupid things we did.
When you got busted, you know,
whether I was a cop or not,
you know, if there was
anything I could've done,
I would've done it,
and I just want you
to know that.
Is that why you let
that dude go in L.A.?
Yeah. I think that had
a lot to do with it.
When I got busted,
it wasn't your fault.
It was all on me,
Mr. Roman Pearce...
wild-and-out crazy, man.
No one can tell me
nothin;
- Ridin' solo.
- Yeah, well, not anymore.
Not anymore, bro.
I got Verone's Navigator
leavin' the residence.
Copy. Sir, we've got
Verone on the move
to the airstrip.
Good. Let's get a bird
in the air. Tell him
to keep his distance.
Good and tight.
Ready to go.
Channel two. Channel two.
You're all set.
Thanks.
All set?
Yep. Let's do it.
Report.
What's goin'on out there?
- Team one checking in.
- Team two checking in.
- Team three checking in.
- Team four.
All clear here too.
Team five checkin' in.
This is team six.
All clear.
Here we go.
Yeah, so you know what to do.
Just stay cool,
keep focused.
Remember, the airstrip's
on Nallwood Avenue.
It's the third exit
after the bridge.
- Got it.
- So what up, man?
You ready for this?
Come on, man.
Guns, murderers
and crooked cops?
- I was made for this, brah.
Come on.
I got activity at Verone's
trailer property.
Do not move an inch
until I tell you to.
Load up.
All units, move on
the trailer property
right now. Move!
Shit! Local P.D.
Is moving in
on our guys.
Three bags in one car, huh?
Guess so.
Cops.
- I'm not goin' back to jail.
- Where you goin', man?
Let's go! Let's go!
What is he doin'?
Okay, now let's get
the chopper over them.
I want eyes right on top.
You got it.
Lima 25, follow G.P.S.
You know what
you're doin', man?
Stay with me, Rome.
Stay with me.
Come on, man.
I've got 'em
heading south on l-95.
Bring in the aerial E.S.D.'s.
Oh, shit!
- They're catching up, man!
- Shut up, man!
- Yeah, nice drivin', Rome.
Nice drivin'.
- I gotcha, Brian.
Check it out, man!
What was that?
Oh, shit.
- Come on, man.
Take the wheel.
- No. I can't drive.
Just hold the wheel!
I can't drive!
Hold it right there!
Just hold it steady,
just like that.
What are you doin', man?
Que pasa?
Whoo!
Yeah, man!
Hold.
Bilkins,
the bird's in place.
Yeah. We got
Verone's Navigator.
All right.
Money's in transit.
Sit tight.
You're a good driver, man.
Thanks, bro.
We've got the area
blocked ahead.
They've got nowhere to go.
Oh! What was that?
I've got a visual.
Video should be
coming through.
We got it.
Looks good.
Where are they going?
Oh, shit!
All right, Miami's finest,
let's see what you got.
Come on.
Stay with me, boys.
- Hey, man. Everyone's here.
Time for the show.
- Let's give it to 'em.
All right. Let the party
begin. Let's go.
This is unit 2599.
We have the suspects
surrounded.
Holy shit!
It's a scramble, baby.
A big one!
Yeah! Let's do this!
- Check this out!
We're not tracking them
on video.
Must have lost them
in the scramble.
Y'all, let's break.
Yeah!
All right. We got 'em
going west on Beach.
Roger that.
I've got 'em.
Customs has a fix
on two cars going
west on Beach.
Roger. Follow those cars.
Roger that.
Shit.
They're cornered.
Keep your hands
where I can see 'em.!
- Put your hands up.!
- Whoa. Fellas, fellas.
I know my tags are
out of date, but, damn!
What the hell?
Where are they?
Man.! How about them apples,
man?
Yeah! That's some drivin' for
your ass, baby! Ain't that
some drivin' for your ass?
- Good job, man.
- Whatever, man.
You supposed to be
a stone-face killer.
You over there
grabbin' your seat belt.
Hey, Tej. Thanks a lot.
You're the clutch.
I owe you one, big time.
Yeah, Brian, you really
do owe me, man.
You really do... Us.
Suki says you owe us,
right?
- Yo, Rome. You there, man?
Come in.
- What's up, man?
It looks like we got just
one more trick left, huh?
My pleasure, buddy.
Let's do it, baby.
Hey. We should grab Verone
while we still can.
No. Not yet.
What? You lost 'em?
Shit! Those little pricks
are running.
- It's your call.
What do you want to do?
- We're gonna take him down.
He is not leaving here.
Enjoyin' the ride?
Man, it's a fast car, huh?
Man, it's a classic.
Old school.
American muscle.
Man, this car can do
all kinda things, man.
Wanna see?
Check this out
right here, homey.
Yo! What are you
doin', man?
Shut up!
- "Ejecto seato," cuz!
It worked.!
I love this button.!
- Stay on your toes, puto!
Mr. O'Conner,
it worked, baby.
Blow and go.
I'm all clear.
- Meet me at the point.
Hurry up, man. It's on, baby.
- All right. Ten-four, man.
Are you ready?
Let's go!
I got this side.!
Raise your hands!
Get down! Get down!
Get down!
Clear.!
We're clear.!
Back it up.!
It's not Verone and Fuentes.
What do you mean?
Then where the hell
are they?
Get off at Tarpon Point.
Tarpon Point? There's...
There's no airstrip
at Tarpon Point.
Who said anything
about an airstrip?
Brian. Brian, man,
what's the holdup, brah?
- Yo, Rome,
there's a new plan.
- What the hell?
We're meeting them at
the Tarpon Point exit,
not the airstrip.
- So what are you sayin'?
- Like I said,
there's a new plan.
Brian. Brian, hello?
You there?
Damn!
Yo! What the hell
is he doin'?
The feds are in the wrong place.
Brian's woman is on her own
with Verone.
- So...
- So Brian's not comin'.
- It's all right.
Let him out.
- Get out.
Pop the trunk.
Hurry up.
- Where's the rest of it?
- The other car.
- Another car.
Where's the other car?
- On it's way.
- On the way, huh?
- Yeah. Here's your money.
So you know nothing
about the agents
that stormed my jet?
The funny thing is that
I only told one person
about the airstrip.
Hmm.
Customs agents sure
are gettin' pretty,
aren't they?
Put her on the boat.
- Let's go.
- Get on the boat.
- Hide the cars
and get rid of him.
- Back in the car.
End of the road.
You know, I like you,
but I still gotta kill you.
It's my job.
- What's that?
- It's Barstow, baby!
It's about to get ugly!
Let's go.
Get your...
Oh, shit!
Come on.
You had me.
You slipped.
Eleven and a half months,
and you slipped once.
Put her downstairs.
I'll see you
in a second.
I thought you was dead, man.
Yeah. Me too. Thanks
for saving my ass, bro.
What are you doin', Brian?
I don't know,
but if Verone sees a helicopter
or Customs boat, she's dead.
Boat. Car.
Boat... You're not gonna do
what I think you're gonna do?
- Yeah, I think so.
You got my back, bro?
- Yeah.
- Put on a seat belt.
- Show 'em some real
Dukes of Hazzard shit.
We're gonna do this big.
Hold on, Rome. Hold on.
Oh.! Brian, you crazy, man.!
What the hell you doin'?
- Brian, what the hell
you doin'?
Whoa!
Shit!
My arm. I think
I broke my arm, man.
Get the gun.
It's over, Carter.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I'm great.
We got 'em, man.
We got 'em.
Let's get outta here.
Go! Go!
That ought to do it.
So, there were
three bags total, huh?
The three from the boat.
So we good, right?
My record's clean?
You held up your end.
Your records are clean.
So maybe
there was six bags.
I guess we can
call it even.
Agent Dunn.
Sir.
We found some
more evidence.
Come on.
Let's take it
to the truck.
Don't drop the soap,
big homey.
I hope you know
that when he gets out,
he's gonna kill your ass.
He ain't gettin' out.
- I'll see you soon.
- You think
he gonna get out?
He'll be out.
No, for real. You think
he gettin' out, though?
We took care
of your decoys.
They're free and clear.
There's a sedan
out on the road
for you.
Try to bring it back
in one piece.
Yeah.
- Thanks a lot, Bilkins.
You're all right.
- Thanks.
- Thanks for lookin' out, man.
- All right.
- So you trust me now?
- You right.
Sorry.
Nice working
with you, O'Conner.
Same here.
Mm. I'm-a have to stay
out here in Miami, man.
Keep you out
of trouble, brah.
You know what
I'm talkin' about.
So you gonna kick it
in Miami, bro?
Oh, man,
I love Miami.
Miami's
off the hook.
Open a garage together.
A garage?
How we gonna
do that, brah?
Pockets ain't empty, cuz.
And we ain't hungry
no more either, brah.
*Pump, p-p-pump, pump
P-P-P-Pump *
*Pump, p-p-pump
Pump it up *
Pump, p-pump, p-pump *
*Pump, p-p-pump, pump it up
Just blaze *
*Pump, p-p-pump, pump it up *
* We gonna do it like
uh, uh, uh *
*Look, pump it up if you came
to get it krunk with a dame
and shit that's drunk *
* You came to get it on
More than five O's
in your bank *
* Then get it on
Roll up like that stank
and get it on *
*Slank that fitted on
Came to get it on *
*Hold up, she want work
that twork that *
* Then again
let me hurt that murk that
till you gotta hurt back *
* Can't spit it out
Boo, you gotta slurp that *
* Can't cuddle after we done
It wasn't worth that *
*Joey, I'm responsible
for bringin'her back *
*And we bad, huh *
*She at the bar stylin'
She throwin'it up *
*She drink a little hypno
throwin'it up *
*But I'm only dealin'
with freaks that wanna cut *
*Ma, if you agree
I want nut *
* Camcorder, get it played
late night on B.E.T. Uncut
Uh *
*Fellas, do your thing
Let me do my thing *
*I mean, do your thing
*Shorties, move that thing
Mami, move that thing *
* Come on, move that thing
*Hustlers, do your thing
Let me do my thing *
*Please tell the deejay *
*Pump, p-p-pump
Pump it up *
*I see some haters grillin'
I see some ladies chillin'*
*I see dat girlie
I been plottin'to get *
*She can hop in the web
and we can *
*Pump, p-p-pump, Pump it up *
* Okay, we was leavin'
We was done *
* Then she said
Can my peoples come *
*Here we go
I see it don't stop *
* They wanna ride in somethin'
where the rims don't stop *
*Look, baby, you fine
but your girlfriend's not *
*Fellas, do your thing
Let me do my thing *
*I mean, do your thing
*Shorties, move that thing
Mami, move that thing *
* Come on, move that thing
*Hustlers, do your thing
Let me do my thing *
*Please tell the deejay *
*Pump, p-p-pump
Pump it up *
*Fellas, do your thing
Let me do my thing *
*I mean, do your thing
*Shorties, move that thing
Mami, move that thing *
* Come on, move that thing
*Hustlers, do your thing
Let me do my thing *
*Please tell the deejay *
*Pump, p-p-pump
Pump it up **
*Drah *
*2 fast *
*2 furious *
*I'm too fast for y'all, man *
*Drah *
*2 fast *
*2 furious *
* Oh, I'm too fast
for y'all, man *
*Ahh, you just came home
from doin'a bid *
* Tell me what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Somebody broke in
and cleaned out your crib *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Just bought a new pair
and they scuffed your shoes *
* Tell me what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Now them cops
tryin'to throw you
in them county blues *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
* Talkin' 'bout traps
cops and robbers *
*It's 911
Please call the doctor *
*Evacuate the building
and trick the pigs *
*Since everybody want a piece
we gonna split your wigs *
*See, some fools slipped up
and overstepped
they boundaries *
* You 'bout to catch a cold
Stay the f... from around me *
* Ya peeps talkin' 'bout
what kinda sh... 's he on *
* You disappear like
poof, b... be gone *
* You think 12 gonna catch me
Gimme a break *
*I'm supercharged with
the hideaway license plates *
*It seems they wanna
fingerprint me
and gimme some years *
* They'll only get one finger
while I'm shifting gears *
*I got suede on my roof
wood grain on the dash *
*Sheepskin on the rug
Golden Grain in the stash *
*Hydraulics all around
so I shake the ride *
* We go front, back
and side to side *
*Some punk just tripped up
and made you
spill your drink *
* Tell me what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Now your carjust stopped
on an empty tank *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*lf you got late bills
and you lost yourjob *
* Tell me what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*lf you 'bout to get drunk
and you ready to mob *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Let's take it to the streets
'cause I'm ready to cruise *
*Just bought me and my cars
all some brand-new shoes *
*And the peoplejust stare
so I love to park it *
*And I just put a computer
in the glove compartment *
* With my pedal to the floor,
radar in the grill *
* TVin the middle
of my steerin'wheel *
*It's my car's birthday
so we blowin'them candles *
*More speakers in the trunk
than my ride can handle *
* Got my name in the headrest
Read it and weep *
*NOS tank in the back
camel hair on the seat *
*And when I pull up to the club
I get all the affection *
* 'Cause the women
love the paint and they
can see their reflection *
*I'm about to take off
so "F"what ya heard *
*Because my side mirrors flap
like a f... n'bird *
*And for the fools
we gonna clock one
Then we'll f... one *
* 'Cause my folk ridin'shotgun
with a sh... *
* You just got hustled
for a wad of cash *
*Man, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Now your friends
just smoked up
your brand-new stash *
*Say, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Now them girls up the block
still runnin'they mouth *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*lf anyone talk bad
'bout the dirty south *
* Tell me what I'm gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*I got my eyes wide shut
and my trunk wide open *
*Did donuts last week, and
the streets still smokin'*
*See, I'm off that antifreeze
and my car is tipsy *
* On the off-ramp doin'
'bout 150 *
*Rollin'through East Pernium
on my way to Ben Heel *
*Slide a five to thejunkie
to clean my windshield *
* Got the whole crew ridin'
and we startin'... *
*I even got a trailer hitch
with a barbecue pit *
*And now all you wanna do
is get drunk and pout *
*Plus your new name is Fire
'cause we stomped you out *
*And, yeah, we...
trees and bees
That's fantastic *
*So, girls, hold your weave
while I'm weavin'
through traffic *
*I kicked to fifth gear
and tear the road apart *
* You'll be like littleJohn "Q"
and get a change ofheart *
*It's one mission, two clips
and some triple beams *
*I'm about to blow this
whole sh... up
to smithereens *
*Ahh, you just came home
from doin'a bid *
* Tell me what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Somebody broke in
and cleaned out your crib *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Just bought a new pair
and they scuffed your shoes *
* Tell me what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Now them cops
tryin'to throw you
in them county blues *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
* Talkin' 'bout pot holes
in the street
just bent ya rims *
* Tell me what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*Man, that ain't sticky
That's sticks and stems *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
* Catch your man with another
b... up in your bed *
*Ladies, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*lf the bottle's all gone
and your eyes are red *
*Boy, what you gonna do *
*Act a fool *
*2 fast, 2 fast
2 furious, 2 furious *
*2 fast, 2... *
*Act a fool *
*2 fast, 2 fast
2 furious, 2 furious *
*2 fast, 2... *
*Act a fool *
*2 fast, 2 fast
2 furious, 2 furious *
*2 fast, 2... *
*Act a fool *
*2 fast, 2 fast
2 furious, 2 furious *
*2 fast, 2... *
*Act a fool **