JUDGE: Dominic Toretto.
You are hereby sentenced
to serve 25 years to life
at the Lompoc Maximum Security
Prison system
without the possibility
of early parole.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Here's what we know so far.
This is all the aftermath
of a daring,
daylight breakout.
There were 26 high-risk
inmates being transferred...
A daring midday breakout
where everyone onboard
has been accounted for,
except for one,
Dominic Toretto.
Police have
just released the identity
of the man they believe
to have orchestrated
the shocking escape
that amazingly resulted
in no fatalities
this afternoon.
He is former federal agent,
Brian O'Conner.
A fierce manhunt is underway
for three fugitives tonight.
Multiple federal
and local agencies
have joined forces
in the search
for Dominic Toretto
and his accomplices
Brian O'Conner
and Mia Toretto.
But despite every eye
in the country
looking for them
where Toretto
and O'Conner are now
is anyone's guess.
It's got to be it, right?
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPING)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(GUNS COCKING)
Let's get out of here.
VINCE: Whoa, whoa!
(VINCE SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Easy, friends.
She's with me.
(LAUGHING)
Mia.
Vince.
Buster.
Come on.
Dom here yet?
No.
When was the last time
you heard from him?
A couple of weeks ago.
Up in Ecuador somewhere.
VINCE: How does it feel?
What's that?
To be on the other side
of a wanted poster?
He'll show up.
Yeah.
Dom's?
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Time for bed little one.
Can I bring him?
Of course.
MIA: Aw.
Good night.
(BABY CRYING)
Excuse me, sorry.
Why Rio, Vince?
(SIGHS)
You mean after you
screwed everything up in LA?
Ended up free-falling
through South America,
you know,
hitting every hellhole
on the way down.
Would have kept
on going if not for Rosa.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Does he know?
So, listen.
There is a job coming up.
I was hoping Dom
was going to be here by now
but this one is clean enough
we can do it without him.
It's a good gig.
Couple of high-end cars,
easy targets.
Guy I know is putting
together a team
to swipe them.
Just need a few more
willing bodies.
I don't know.
Look, the way the car
scene is down here
we can unload them quick
and get top dollar.
It's easy money.
And from where I'm sitting,
it looks like you both
could use the payday.
(ENGINE REVVING)
What are you reading?
Travel guide.
Yeah?
Tokyo.
Moscow.
Goa.
You want to know
what all of these places
have in common?
Huh?
No extradition.
Here we go.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
Excuse me, buddy.
Okay.
Hey, we've found them.
Yeah, second-to-the-last
freighter.
What is it?
DEA tags. These cars
have been seized.
Look who showed up.
God, I'm so happy you're okay.
I thought I told you
to lay low.
Been running on fumes.
Had to make a call.
Hey! Quit talking.
We only got
the two-minute window.
Let's go, Vince.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
I'm taking the GT40.
Ladies first.
Hey!
MIA: Hey!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
This car suits me better.
See you, baby.
It's okay...
we're all going
to the same place.
We'll get the car there.
Change of plans.
Wait for my call.
Let's go!
Where is she going?
Hey!
We're being robbed!
Whatever happens,
don't stop the train!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Go after the girl!
Hurry up!
Access card!
Get the access card!
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(SCREAMING)
Shit.
(GRUNTING)
Bridge! There is a bridge!
(ENGINE REVVING)
Luggage car is clear.
Freeze!
Oh, shit!
(COUGHING)
You had to make a call, huh?
Shitty call, O'Conner.
Shitty call.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
You two stirred up
quite a bit of trouble today.
Three of my men dead.
Three DEA agents
along with them.
Of course,
this is business
and sometimes
things go astray.
All I care about is the car.
Tell me where it is,
and I'll let you go.
BRIAN: This roofing plastic
says you're full of shit.
(REYES LAUGHING)
I don't know how you guys
do business in your part
of the world,
but here in Rio,
I like it when all parties
know what they're up against.
DOM: That's funny.
Because it goes both ways.
You know,
I hear your sister
is very beautiful.
Wherever she hides
I will find her.
(SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
(NEWSCASTER SPEAKING
PORTUGUESE)
The American fugitives
killed three DEA agents
during a train robbery...
...Police warn
they are armed and
extremely dangerous.
Anyone with information
should contact law
enforcement immediately...
(DOOR OPENING)
BRIAN: Mia?
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah, you all right?
Hey.
Hey, yeah.
Just like a Toretto.
Where's Vince?
That's a good question.
He'll be here.
Guys, we're all over
the news.
They're blaming us
for the killing of those
DEA agents on the train.
Which means we just jumped
to the top of the wanted list.
The feds have got
to show everyone
their agents are off limits
and they're going to send
their best guys. We got
to get out of here.
One thing we know for sure
is that they wanted this car.
Because something is in it.
If we find out what it is,
we'll know what we're
up against.
HOBBS: All right, listen up!
The men we're after
are professional runners.
They like speed and are
guaranteed to go down
the hardest possible way
so make sure you got
your funderwear on.
We find them, we take them
as a team, and we bring
them back.
And above all else,
we don't ever, ever let
them get into cars.
Crime scene is 10 hours old
and counting, men.
Let's go hunting.
Agente Hobbs!
Chief of Police,
João Alemeida.
Luke.
Sorry to hear about
the loss of your men.
Is all this really necessary
to apprehend two men?
Let me tell you something
about these two men.
One is a former federal
officer, been in deep cover
for five years.
He knows every way
you're going to come
for him.
The other one is
a professional criminal,
escaped prison twice,
spent half his life
on the run avoiding
folks like you.
Well, if there's anything
we can do to help the DSS...
Two things.
One, I need a translator.
We have plenty
in the public relations
department.
Elena Neves.
A patrol officer?
You heard me.
But why?
We have many
more experienced people.
I like her smile.
What's the second thing?
Stay the fuck out of my way.
(DRILLING)
Brian.
Hm?
I have something
I have to tell you.
(DOOR OPENING)
VINCE: God damn.
What a mess!
Where you been, man?
(CHUCKLING)
You better check that tone.
And you just better answer
the goddamn question.
Stop it!
Both of you.
Where were you, Vince?
Guys all over
the favelas asking
about you.
Couldn't get out of there
without leading them
straight to you.
Had to wait them out.
That is such horseshit.
(SHOUTING) That was your job,
and those were your guys!
Hey!
Hey! Enough, O'Conner!
If he said he didn't do it,
he didn't do it.
Go walk it off.
REYES: Look, I would love
to expand my operations
into your countries
but, quite frankly,
your business methods
are too violent.
Let me tell you a true story.
Five hundred years ago,
the Portuguese
and the Spanish came here,
each trying to get the country
from their natives.
The Spaniards arrived,
guns blazing, determined
to prove who was boss.
The natives killed
every single Spaniard.
Personally, I prefer
the methods of the Portuguese.
They came bearing gifts.
Mirrors, scissors, trinkets.
Things that the natives
couldn't get on their own,
but to continue receiving
them, they had to work
for the Portuguese.
And that's why
all Brazilians speak
Portuguese today.
Now, if you dominate
the people with violence,
they will eventually
fight back because
they have nothing to lose.
And that's the key.
I go into the favelas
and give them
something to lose.
Electricity, running water,
school rooms for their kids.
And for that taste
of a better life,
I own them.
Gentlemen.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
I apologize for
the interruption.
Señor Reyes,
may I speak with you?
We've found them.
Pardon me, gentlemen.
DOM: Almost wish
I didn't see that.
Almost.
Wait, Dom.
Mia was on that train.
(SHOUTING)
My sister!
I didn't know.
I wouldn't do
anything to hurt her.
You set up the deal!
I thought the job
was for the cars.
I didn't know.
All they want is the chip.
Damn!
You should've come clean.
What's going on out here?
Nothing.
Please, Dom, just let
me have the chip.
I can take this to them.
They'll give it to Reyes
and set things right.
Get out.
What?
Get out!
You never listen to me.
Not when I told you
he was a cop, and not now.
You never trust me
and look where it's gotten us.
Look at our family now.
I can't go home!
Your sister is stuck
in this life!
Where's Letty, Dom?
Where's Letty?
Plasma cutter.
Wilkes, I want a list
of every place within 50 miles
that distributes
compressed gas tanks.
Pass me that manifest.
Officer Neves.
Been waiting for you.
You asked for me?
I did.
May I ask why?
My smile
is not that great.
Your husband was
an officer who was
gunned down in the favela.
Six months later,
you upped and joined
the force.
You're motivated.
Plus, I figure you're
the only one in Rio
who can't be bought.
Am I right?
Yes.
Of course I am.
Good news, bad news.
You know I like
my dessert first.
Back-checked
the rail line like you asked.
Found a couple of spots
where they unloaded the cars.
One set of tracks
headed west
until it hit the main highway,
then disappeared.
But another set
of tracks headed east.
A 107-inch wheelbase,
eight-and-a-half-inch tread.
The GT40 that was missing
from the manifest.
Followed the trail
a couple of miles.
Pretty easy in this scrub.
Can't move without
leaving a sign.
Give me the damn veggies.
The ground rolls into
a hardpack and we lost
that track, too.
Not necessarily.
That road heads up
through the hills
into the favelas.
Couple of years ago,
it was washed out by a storm.
It's all dirt a mile
from where you were.
If they headed that way,
we'll pick up
their tracks there.
You come prepared.
I'm motivated.
HOBBS: All right, then.
Let's find ourselves a car.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
What do you think?
Well, it's definitely
a custom chip.
Look at all these side menus
here for data entry.
Let's check this one.
Look at that.
Same building,
same order every week.
It's a delivery schedule.
What's this?
Drugs?
No. That's a dealer pack.
See, most major players,
they weigh their money
so they don't have
to constantly count it.
Right there,
that's 49 kilos.
49 kilos is a million
in twenties.
You're saying each one
of these shipments
is worth 10 million dollars?
Yeah.
(GUN COCKING)
I thought so.
So what is that?
A 100-million plus
in cash houses?
That's how he keeps it
off the grid.
I think it's safe to say
that Reyes is smart
to want this back.
It's his whole network
right there, just laid
out on a chip.
(GLASS TINKLING)
(YELLING)
Wilkes, Fusco,
up the middle.
Mac, Chato,
flank north.
What about me?
Stay here.
(YELLING)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Go that way!
The other two
went over the wall!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Come on, go! Go!
(YELLING)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Get on the ground.
I got Toretto.
Four blocks north of your...
They already know
who you are.
(YELLING IN PORTUGUESE)
(GASPS)
Let's go.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
You okay here?
Yeah. I'm good.
Thank you.
They're going to be looking
for the three of us
together now.
We need to split up.
You and Mia head south,
I'll lead them away.
No.
Dom is right.
Look how lucky we just got.
What happens next time?
We have no choice
but to split up.
I'm pregnant.
I already lost
my family once.
I'm not going through
that again.
Are you kidding me?
No.
I'm not going
anywhere. Okay?
Dom?
Promise me
we stick together.
I promise.
Our family
just got bigger.
Something
doesn't add up.
Toretto and O'Conner.
They stay when they're
supposed to run, they steal
gas then give it away?
Now they're killing
federal agents?
It doesn't make any sense.
Here's what makes sense.
All these guys are
is names on a list.
They come up,
we take them down.
Not a phone call more,
not a bullet less.
Wilkes, we get anything?
Standard forensics.
Shoe prints.
Hair and fiber.
Prints are all over the car.
Anything else?
Yeah, we tracked the owner
off the vehicle ID.
There are a couple
of shell companies
in between,
but we finally
traced it back
to a corporation
owned by an investor
down here named
Hernan Reyes.
Investor?
If there's anything
illegal happening in Rio,
Reyes is involved.
Okay, then so are we.
If he could get us
any closer to our guys,
I want everything on him.
Chato, you're
on the roof.
I want you on overwatch
in case somebody comes
back for something.
Mac, give me a cross-check
on Reyes, full specs.
If he goes to the john,
I want to know how
many times he shakes it.
You got it, boss.
Wilkes, Fusco!
Let's put all this
mess back together.
That's going to take a while.
Then you better get started.
They were taking
this car apart for a reason.
Let's put it back together
and find out what's missing.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Hey, Dom,
what do you remember
about your father?
My father.
He used to...
He used to have a barbecue
every Sunday after church.
For anybody
in the neighborhood.
If you didn't go to church,
you didn't get any barbecue.
Every single day he was
in the shop, and every
single night,
he was at the kitchen table
with Mia, helping her
with her homework.
Even after she went to sleep,
he'd stay up
for a few more hours
so he could learn
the next chapter
and help her the next day.
I remember everything
about my father.
Everything.
That's just it.
I don't remember shit
about my dad.
I don't remember
him yelling.
him smiling.
To be honest with you,
I don't even remember
what the hell he looked like.
I don't remember.
He just...
He was just never there.
You ain't going
to be like that, Brian.
We can't keep
running, Dom.
We got to get out.
We got to get out now.
You're right.
Here's how we're
going to do it.
We're going to use this.
We're going do one last job.
We're going to take
all of Reyes' money.
Every dime of it,
and disappear.
Forever.
New passports.
New lives
with no more looking
over our shoulder.
And we're just going
to buy our freedom.
That's right.
You realize we're
talking about going
up against
the most powerful guy
in all of Rio?
Yes, we are.
Then we're going
to need a team.
Let's run through
the bases real quick.
Who do we got?
First we're going
to need a chameleon.
Someone who can
blend in anywhere.
What else?
A fast talker.
Someone who can
bullshit their way
out of anything.
I got that.
This guy is going to have
a lot of surveillance.
We're going to need someone
who's good with circuits.
DOM: And with those circuits,
Reyes is going to have walls.
We're going to need guys
to punch through those walls.
MIA: What else?
Utilities and weapons.
Someone who ain't
afraid to throw down.
Someone to back up
every position.
BRIAN: Yeah, what else
do we need?
DOM: Most importantly,
we're going to need
two precision drivers.
Guys that don't crack
under pressure.
Guys that never lose.
You know we got that.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(HIP HOP BEAT PLAYING
ON CAR STEREO)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Aw, hell, no!
I see they really scraped
the bottom of the barrel, huh?
I guess they did,
since your ass is here.
When are you going
to give Martin Luther King
his car back?
As soon as you give
Rick James his jacket back.
(LAUGHING)
What's up, man?
What's up?
Hmm.
Sexy legs,
baby girl.
What time do they open?
They open the same time
as I pull this trigger.
Want me to open them?
(TEGO SPEAKING SPANISH)
I told you the skinny
chick had balls.
Looks like she started
the party without us.
Hey, anybody can talk shit
in Spanish, homie.
What's this guy saying?
Ugly is still ugly in
Spanish or in English.
(BOTH TAUNTING IN SPANISH)
Who are these clowns, man?
Circus clowns.
(ALL CHATTERING ANGRILY)
I thought cockfights
were illegal in Brazil.
I see you all have met.
You know when you called me
to come to Rio
I assumed it would be
for something more
exciting than this.
Look at this guy.
Long time.
I missed you, man.
Good to see you.
Brother.
What's up?
Yo, check this out.
This is Tej.
Best circuit man
on the East Coast.
And this is my boy,
Roman Pearce.
We go way back,
I met this guy in juvie.
I pulled that job
with him in Miami.
I've heard about you.
Nice digs.
Yeah, well,
the Ritz was sold out.
So what's this
all about, Dom?
Yeah, man, why did
you drag us halfway
around the world?
Because we got a job.
All right,
so our target's name
is Hernan Reyes.
And he runs
the drug scene down here.
He's never been busted
because he doesn't
leave a paper trail.
No paper trail
means no banks.
And no banks means
cash houses.
That's right.
Ten of them,
to be exact.
Spread throughout the city.
And we're going
to hit them all.
All of them?
All of them.
That sounds crazy.
You bring us
to a whole other country
so we can rob
the dude who runs it?
I thought this was business.
Sounds personal to me.
Is that what this is?
I got love for y'all,
but personal ain't
good business.
I can't do this, homie.
So what we're talking
about is $100 million.
You say what?
Hundred...
See, sometimes I be
over thinking, man,
and I know we just met,
but you just, kind of,
got to...
That's right, $100 million,
and everything we take,
we split even.
TEJ: That's a little over
$11 million apiece.
I am down.
I'm in.
Eleven million.
Sounds like a whole lot of
vaginal activity to me.
You can't pull off 10 heists
on the same mark.
You just can't.
As soon as we hit
the first one,
they're going to do
everything they can
to protect the rest.
Exactly.
(CASH MACHINES WHIRRING)
(DOORBELL BUZZING)
(GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Nobody move!
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
That's all of it.
You a dead man.
You're all dead men!
You don't have
a place to hide.
Who's hiding?
THUG: Are you crazy?
Are you crazy?
Do you know whose house
this is? Whose money
are you stealing?
We ain't stealing it.
You tell your boss
exactly who did this.
Tell him there's more coming.
Voilà.
Turn it over.
(ENGINE STARTING)
She's running on all eight.
Checks out fine.
Keep looking.
(SIGHING)
Boss, if something
was missing, we'd know.
It's a goddamn shame
putting bullshit
like that on a classic.
You may as well slap
neon lights on it.
(BEEPING)
They took the chip.
We got a hit on the police
scanner. Armed robbery at
a house in Leblon.
Address cross-checks
against property
owned by one
of Hernan Reyes' corporations.
All right,
if that's our guys
then whatever was on
that chip led them
directly to that house.
It's them, for sure.
How do you know that?
Because no one else in Rio
is stupid enough to rob Reyes.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Explain.
They invaded
the Leblon house.
Who invaded?
The men from the train.
How much did they take?
They didn't
take anything.
They burned it!
They burned my money?
Yes. And said
there's more coming.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Okay...
Then this...
...is what
we're going to do.
Clean the houses.
I want that money
under lock and key...
...within an hour.
Understand?
Understood.
Number One
is on the move, man.
ROME: Two is on the move.
I got mine.
I got eyes on Five.
I know y'all said
they were consolidating
the money somewhere, but,
y'all ain't going
to believe this.
Well, this job just got
a lot harder.
If he's moving it
into a police station
he's got some serious
brass in his pocket.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Looks like this is going
to be a shorter trip
than I thought...
Hell, yeah,
we can't do this.
"Can't"? You mean,
"shouldn't."
I think this doesn't
change a thing.
I say we stick to the plan.
You say what?
This just went
from Mission: Lmpossible
to Mission:
In-freaking-sanity.
Whatever, man.
I ain't scared, I'm just
letting you all know, going
in that building is crazy.
BRIAN: I got this.
What time
was the robbery?
Around 11:00.
Here we go.
Enhance it.
Their faces are covered.
Run it through FRS.
Well, hello,
you son of a bitch.
Wilkes! Run the photos
of known associates
of Toretto and O'Conner
against customs entries
into Brazil in the last
two weeks.
Check planes, trains,
boats, everything short
of the goddamn space shuttle.
They can change their names
but they can't change
their faces.
Something big
is going down.
That's a 1970 Charger.
Fusco! Upload these specs
into the database.
Have the computer cross-check
it with overhead satellites
every 15 minutes,
the van behind it, too.
If these vehicles move
in the streets of Rio,
I want to know about it.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Everything okay?
Everything is okay.
Who is this Hobbs?
This Federal Agent
running around town?
Some American cowboy.
He's handled.
He killed sixteen
of our men.
Handle him better.
Look... He requested
a rookie patrol officer
as his assistant.
They won't be a problem.
It's all here?
Yes.
What about Toretto
and O'Conner?
Where are they?
Nothing yet.
But I have all our
officers searching.
Not good enough.
Put a price
on their heads.
High enough...
...to get every pair
of eyes in the city
searching for them.
The beauty of public offices?
Public records.
This is where he's keeping
the money. The vault
in the evidence room.
Um. Uh, yeah. Can I get
everyone's attention,
right here, for a second?
We're talking about
breaking into
a police station.
Is anyone listening
to those words?
Anybody? Popo?
Five-O. One-time. Pigs.
People we don't like.
You know, police stations
are designed to keep
people in, not out.
That's why it's
a stealth mission.
We'll be in and out
before they even know
we were there.
Well, we'll need
to get eyes in there.
At least to find out
the make and model
of that vault.
So the vault
and then, so...
It's crazy.
Who's supposed
to do all this?
What do you mean?
Why me?
Because you got
the biggest mouth.
That's for damn sure.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(HUMMING)
Ooh.
Hello, beautiful.
Look at those dimples.
Sexy, sexy.
Love those glasses.
Where did you get them from?
Are those like Gucci frames
or something?
No English?
No, no, no. Damn.
How are you, sir?
Special Agent O'Conner.
US Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
It says Caucasian.
That's a tan.
You know, a tan?
Look, I'm working
this case and I got some
evidence here to be held.
But I need to get in
and check your
storage facility first.
Nope.
Look, I know you're
a true professional,
and I respect you, I promise.
You know, it looks like
you work out
a little bit, too.
What do you bench,
about 350?
Ah, shit.
Look, I'm just trying
to do my job, man.
My boss sent me here
to just make sure
that everything was safe.
It will be safe.
Let me just come in
and take a quick peek.
Nope.
Come on, man.
Hook a brother up,
please?
Nope. And you're
not my brother.
Brother from
another mother?
Look! No one enters
the facility but authorized
evidence personnel.
Now stop wasting my time.
I'm going to call
the embassy.
No, no, no!
No, we're good.
We don't need to call them.
For what? We're good.
Here, I got the box.
We're all good.
I promise you.
Thank you so much
for your time.
Swear to God, if you
were on the other
side of that glass
I'd bust your damn face in.
Now translate that.
It's done. See, I think
I make a better special
agent than you ever did.
(LAUGHING)
Well, that depends
on how you define "special."
TEJ: Come on, now.
Let's see what we got.
Not funny.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
All right, come on.
Dawg,
you still can't drive.
Now, I see why
you're always
getting into accidents.
You can't even drive
a damn remote control car.
I'm going to need you
to shut up right now.
I'm not going to shut up.
Shut up.
Strap him in his
safety belt, man.
Give me the remote,
dawg. Go left.
It looks like something
right over there
to the left. What is that?
BRIAN: What is that?
Bingo.
What is that,
six-by-six?
Eight-by-twelve.
Seven-by-twelve.
Fitted with 18-inch-thick
steel reinforced walls
with a insulated copper
core to protect
against thermal lance.
A Class-3 electronic
lock with a surefire
Griffin retumbler
and a biometric palm scanner.
Ten tons of
top-of-the-line security.
Do I want to know
how you know all that?
I had a life before
you knew me, O'Conner.
Let's just leave it
at that, all right?
She is a beauty,
though, man.
A "beauty"
as in "good"?
"Beauty" as in, she's
going to start off
playing hard to get.
Then, no matter how much
I caress her, no matter
how much I love her,
in the end,
she still ain't going
to give up that ass.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Two to one says
you blow the wrong pipe.
Yo, why you got to be
so negative all the time, man?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I ain't negative.
I'm just positive
you're going to mess it up.
I'm telling you, man,
you got issues.
Next time if
there's no elevator,
I'm not coming.
You need to learn
to relax, loco.
(TIMER BEEPING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
You better hurry up,
we got less than a minute.
Why do you always set
the timer so short?
(SCREAMING)
(RICO SPEAKING SPANISH)
I hope you know
where you're going.
I got this. Relax, man.
Relax.
(WHIMPERS)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
...a police station.
Relax.
(EXCLAIMS)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
You used too much
explosive! Again.
Too much, too little...
It's all the same.
That's some Buddha shit
you learned from a book in
the prison library, isn't it?
And what you're doing
there on the wall...
You got that from
the same book, huh?
You're so negative, bro.
Can I have some light?
MIA: Got it. We got it!
BRIAN: Yeah, we're looking
at four cameras.
Yo, that's some
high-end shit, too.
Marker optics.
Hundred-degree
field-of-view.
Ten seconds oscillation.
Yeah, that's
a narrow window, man.
Can't we just tap in
and replace the image?
No, it's hooked
into a digital sync.
They would know we were
in the system.
The best we can do is peek.
We're going to need
some real fast cars
to get through this.
Not just fast.
You got a hard right
and a hairpin.
We're going to need
something agile.
You guys mock up a track.
O'Conner.
Let's go get some cars.
Nice.
Home sweet home.
(LAUGHING)
BRIAN: Or that.
How about that?
All motor, no tuning issues.
I always wanted one of those.
Held the record
on the Avenida
three years running.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Damn, bro...
You got a lot of balls
to bring your problems
here, Toretto.
Not to mention a cop.
Yeah, we can keep
that on the low.
Word on the street is
a lot of people are
looking for you two.
What?
You didn't think
we'd recognize you?
No, we're kind
of counting on it.
That little coupe
may run the streets
around here,
but that monster
has never seen
a set of tail lights.
Ever.
Well, she's about to.
(DIOGO SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Dominic Toretto's
ride in my garage.
Now that...
will be a nice trophy.
Let's go, legend.
Car for car.
Car for car?
DIOGO: You want it,
come and get it.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Let's see what they got.
(ROME LAUGHING)
Really?
Where did you get
that from? Papa Smurf?
Okay, O'Conner,
give it your best shot.
How was that one?
Camera caught you.
What?
Yeah, it still caught you.
Man, I was milking
the hell out of
that thing, too.
We're going to need
a faster car.
(SHOUTING INCOMPREHENSIBLY)
I want my money.
Come on, man.
Yeah!
Let's get it! Watch this.
That's exactly why your ass
ain't been driving.
I think I'm in love.
That was real solid work.
I think Camera 3
still caught you, though.
Let's do it again.
TEGO: That's the piggy bank
you ordered.
You're kidding me.
Yep.
Where in the hell
did y'all get one of these?
Well, we had a life
before you met us.
All right, I'll get to work
on the electronic tumbler
but there's still
another problem.
Palm scanner.
And without Reyes' handprint,
Houdini himself
couldn't open this bitch.
How do you know
it's Reyes' handprint?
You got $100 million
in a safe.
You going to put
somebody else's
handprint on it?
(TALKING SPANISH)
Now there you go
with that negativity, man.
That shit is eating
you alive.
You check that.
Yo, check that.
Shut up!
How are we supposed to get
Reyes' handprint?
DOM: Han.
You're up.
Sure. Nothing like
the easy stuff.
Let's go. I'll drive.
I make six bodyguards.
Seven.
You think that guy
with a fanny pack
is a tourist?
So, how long were
you in the army?
That gun you pulled
the other day was
a Jericho 941.
Thumb-racking the slide?
That was
straight-up Mossad.
I got out of the military
probably the same time
you quit smoking.
The amount
of chips you eat,
the way you always
have to keep your hands
and mouth busy,
you were a
two-pack-a-day man
for sure.
Unfiltered.
Well, this is a bust.
We're not going to be
able to get his
fingerprints out here.
We need to do some
more recon, call in
a couple of extra guys.
Or
you don't send a man
to do a woman's job.
We're going to figure
this out, I promise you.
What's up?
I thought you were
more of a thong man.
We got the print.
Where?
Okay, that's crazy.
So, did he just slap
that ass or did he grab
and hold on to it?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey, this will work.
TEJ: I'm impressed.
Got it?
TEJ: Got it.
But you still didn't
answer the question.
Oh, no. Guys, guys!
Guys, we have a problem.
The whole team just got burnt.
Now we're all wanted.
GISELE: How did this happen?
US Diplomatic Security Service
issued the warrants.
Agent L. Hobbs.
Hold on one second.
Hey, Dom.
Is that the guy you saw
in the favela?
Yeah.
Hobbs is the leader
of the elite task force
for the DSS.
So he's good.
When the FBI wants
to find somebody,
that's who they call.
Because he never
misses his mark.
This guy is Old Testament.
Blood, bullets, wrath of God.
That's his style.
And right now
he's hunting us?
Dom, we got to move up
our timeline.
ROME: Yeah, but how?
This thing's already been
difficult without Wyatt Earp
on our asses.
If anything,
we need more room
to breathe.
Roman's right.
Think we need to get
some fresh air.
We've got a hit.
'70s Charger.
Let's get a move on!
Eastbound on
Avenida Atlantica.
Move, move, move, move!
It stopped about
a block ahead.
Park it.
We're going on foot.
Hey, Toretto.
You're under arrest.
Arrest?
I don't feel like
I'm under arrest.
How about you,
Brian?
No, not a bit.
Not even a little bit.
Just give it a minute.
It'll sink in.
BRIAN: We didn't kill
those feds. That was Reyes.
HOBBS: I don't give a shit.
I'm just here to bring
in two assholes whose names
hit my desk.
Yeah, that sounds
like a real hero.
That's funny.
From a guy who took the oath
of a cop, then went against
everything it stood for.
Or some wannabe
tough guy prick
who beat a man half
to death with
a socket wrench.
Yeah, real tough.
You turn around
and put your hands
behind your back.
I don't think so.
Your mistake is
thinking you got
a goddamn choice, boy.
And your mistake?
Thinking you're in America.
You're a long way from home.
This is Brazil.
Come on, boss.
Another day.
Come on, H,
it's a lot of heat.
I'll see you soon,
Toretto.
I look forward to it, cop.
Yep.
Tracker's on.
Got them.
I don't understand.
Why come here?
Why risk it all
for $20 worth of silver?
Because it's worth it.
You should run,
you know.
Hobbs will find you.
You have every reason
to leave. Why stay?
Why do you?
My husband was
a good police officer.
An honest man.
We both grew up here.
Two years ago he was
murdered in the street
right outside our door.
Reyes owns this favela now.
He gives things to people.
But everything
has a price.
The people here
need a new start.
They need
to be free.
(SIGHS)
You didn't kill
those men in the train,
did you?
Now, why would you
believe anything
I would tell you?
Hey!
Was she so special to you?
I never thought anyone
could understand how much.
But you do.
Yeah!
Close, but not enough.
Dom, the window
is too small, man.
Only way we're going to
beat the cameras is
with invisible cars.
And I know just where
to get them.
Let's take a ride, boys.
Don't hurt yourself.
It's been a while since
I've been behind the wheel
of one of these.
First time I've ever
been in the front seat.
(CHUCKLES)
Rome, what took
you so long?
I thought for sure you'd be
showing up with some
chrome spinners or something.
Real funny.
I got $100,000 that says
I can take you all
in the next quarter-mile.
Yeah, your broke ass
has got a hundred grand.
If we pull off this job,
I will.
The next two lights.
Hundred thousand.
We don't pull this job off,
we're probably dead anyway.
Let's make it a million.
I like that.
All right,
a million-dollar quarter-mile.
All right, then.
You only live once.
Let's do it.
What do you say, Dom?
We talking or we racing?
Just don't cheat this time.
Got to let that go.
(ENGINES REVVING)
Yeah!
Typical, Roman.
I'm going to get
this money. I'm hungry.
Don't make it too
easy for me, boys.
No!
Not this time, Dom.
You got to want it, Brian.
Yeah! Owned you! Owned you!
Good race, O'Conner.
Thanks, Dom.
Do you know how long
I've been waiting
for that shit?
I told you
he didn't see it.
Your man right there?
He let off the throttle
at the line.
You didn't do nothing.
He let you win.
Bullshit.
(SCOFFING)
Vince, what are you doing?
Quiet! They've been
tracking you.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
I know she's here!
Find her!
Go! Go! Go!
It's okay. Wait!
Reyes' guys were waiting
for me at the market.
Vince saved my life.
DOM: You hungry?
Yeah, sure.
Good.
Because you're saying grace.
Thanks, Vince.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Yo, you burned it!
Yo, this is how my momma
does it. Relax.
Yeah, but your mom is the
worst cook in the world.
Yo, don't you be talking
about my momma.
Yeah, come on, baby.
Who's good living?
To you, bro.
Cheers, cheers, cheers.
ROME: So, we in Brazil.
It's the good life.
Yeah.
So, you got a little more
than $10 or $11 million
coming.
What you going to do
with your money?
Me?
Yeah.
Actually, man, I been
thinking about opening up
a garage back home.
Place where people can
bring their cars and not get
completely ripped off.
You know what I mean?
Really?
Yeah.
So, your dream is
to start a day job?
That's stupid.
Like, why would...
No, it's not stupid at all.
I love what I do.
That don't make
no sense to me.
I know what I'm going
to do with my money.
Buying some cooking lessons
for my man.
See? See?
There you go with
that negativity, man.
You know me.
Money ain't a goddamn thing.
It's going to take
a little more than money
to learn how to cook.
That's horrible.
But I heard they was looking
for a chef down at
this animal shelter.
You might want to...
I know the manager.
Hey, Dom.
Listen.
I know that you're all set
for this job tomorrow,
but if you need
an extra man, I could...
You're in.
There's always
room for family.
Thank you.
Get something to eat.
Yeah.
Can you believe
Mia calls this a curse?
She might be right.
You really like doing
that stuff, huh?
When your life is on
the line that's when you
learn about yourself.
That's a fair deal.
We're less than 24 hours
from the biggest celebration
of our life.
Y'all need a refill.
This is serious stuff.
No, I'm good.
Cheers, baby.
I'm good.
No, thank you.
No, she can't.
What do you mean?
She can't.
What do you mean
she can't? What is...
Are you serious right now?
(LAUGHING)
Is that the reason you let him
beat you in the quarter-mile?
That was a baby gift.
No, that's messed up.
No, you're not taking
that from me.
Wait, wait,
hold on a second.
So, did he just smack
the ass or did he grab
and hold on to it?
Which one was it?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
ROME: How can you keep
this a secret?
Crazy, huh?
ROME: It's your boy.
ROME: Why would you keep
something like that
away from me?
Baby gift, huh?
I have no idea
what they're talking about.
Oh?
TEJ: What happened
to the pull-out method, man?
Toast.
Money will come and go.
We know that.
But the most important
thing in life will always
be the people in this room.
Right here.
Right now.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(ALL REPLYING IN ITALIAN)
I'm all set.
HAN: Yo, Santos. Van good?
You know we're
always good, bro.
Hobbs is on the other side
of the city.
We're not going
to get a better window.
Okay, guys,
it's show time!
First team in position,
let's go.
TEGO: Come on, let's do this.
Hey, Dom.
I got eyes on Mia.
Moscow, Bali, Goa, Hong Kong.
And what do they all
have in common?
No extradition.
We're one hour away
from the rest of our lives.
Yeah.
Cops!
Come on. Go.
You just made a big mistake.
Took me a while to find
that tracking chip.
But not as long
to flip the receiver.
You're going down, Toretto.
I'm right here.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
Dom!
Stand back. I got this.
Pull off!
Dom! Please, stop!
Dom!
(DOM SCREAMING)
(WALKIE TALKIE BEEPING)
Yeah.
We're coming in now.
Have the marshals meet us
at the airport when we land.
Ambush!
Wilkes, suppression fire.
Shut them down.
Stagger-step. Cover me.
Watch them!
Cut us loose!
Come on! Cut us loose!
We're good?
Yeah, let's go, let's go!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SPITTING)
VINCE: Hey, Dom.
You've got to meet my son.
Nico.
I will.
He's a good kid.
You know,
we named him after you.
"Dominic."
You've got
my word, Vince.
You were
always my brother.
I got eyes on Nico now.
We need to move.
We don't have that much time.
I got us a flight out.
We can leave Rio
in the rearview
in the next five hours.
Not to run away.
To finish the job.
Are you crazy, Dom?
We can't.
ROME: It's a suicide mission.
That's your man
over there on the table.
The plan is busted!
This is bullshit, man.
Reyes knows we're coming!
TEJ: He's right.
They tripled the detail
at the police station.
TEJ: It's going to be
a wall of gunfire.
Reyes doesn't get
away with this.
It's a trap, man.
You know that.
Dom, listen to them.
Run, before it's
too late. Leave Rio.
You can be free.
Running ain't freedom.
You should know that.
You know you're all free
to make your own choices.
HOBBS: I'm in.
I'll ride with you,
Toretto.
At least until we kill
that son of a bitch.
BRIAN: So what's
the plan, Dom?
We can't just go
sneaking around anymore.
We don't sneak.
The only thing
he cares about
is his money.
We pull that,
we pull him.
(SECURITY DOOR BUZZING)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
See?
I called in every cop
on our payroll.
We're covered.
We've got every
entrance covered
with weapons teams.
God Himself couldn't
get at your money
if He wanted to.
God isn't my worry.
You ready?
I'm ready.
(POLICE OFFICERS CHATTERING)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
What's happening?
They're taking the vault!
What?
The vault!
Follow me! Quickly!
Let me through!
Don't move!
Stay down.
Call it out, Mia!
You've got a straight shot
for two blocks.
Go right.
Got it.
(PEDESTRIANS SCREAMING)
Well, the plan is working.
You guys have every
corrupt cop in Rio on your
tail. You have to move fast.
What's the best route?
Okay, keep going straight
another half-mile
onto Rua Fonseca,
and then go left.
That ain't going to work.
Spikes ahead, Dom.
We got spikes!
We're going right!
No, it's too tight,
we're not going to fit.
We've got no choice. Now!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Shit!
Holy shit!
Guys, I am hearing
all this chatter. Did you
just take out a bank?
Two inbound!
All right, there's an alley
coming up on your left.
Yeah, I got it.
(GUNSHOTS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
You little bastard!
All right, good job, Dom.
Right-hander, right here,
right-hander.
Guys, there's a big group
coming at you from the south.
You have to do something now!
Hey, go wide.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(CHUCKLING)
Yeah!
(POLICE CAR HONKING)
(BULLETS HITTING CAR)
(GRUNTING)
You're all clear on the left.
Good afternoon, officer!
License and registration,
please!
Yes! This is big-boy stuff!
We're clear on the right.
Oh, man.
Thanks, guys.
Any time.
I'll see you on
the other side.
You guys just carved out
a 10-second window.
Make it count!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Zizi, stay on them.
They can't outrun us
on the bridge.
Shit.
They have no way out.
No!
There's too many of them.
Hey, there's too many of them.
We're not going to make it.
You're right, we aren't.
You are.
What are you talking about?
Just let the vault go.
Get out of there.
You're a father now, Brian.
No, I'm not leaving you.
Now you stick with the plan!
It was always the plan.
Take care of Mia.
Dom, you listen
to me now. Okay?
You cut loose right now.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Hey, what is he doing?
We've got him!
Close down the bridge!
Do something, asshole!
Kill him, dammit!
Kill him now!
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
I thought I told you
to go on.
Yeah, I had
to make a call.
(GROANING)
Help me.
That's for my team,
you son of a bitch.
It's a hell of a mess.
Yeah, it is.
You know I can't
let you two go.
I ain't made that way.
The way I see it,
you've earned
yourselves 24 hours.
The money stays, though.
If I were you,
I'd use the time.
Make peace with
whatever demons
you got left.
Because come tomorrow,
I will find you.
Toretto!
I'll see you soon.
No, you won't.
Thanks, guys.
I'll see you
on the other side.
You guys just carved out
a 10 second window.
Make it count!
(LAUGHING)
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
Come on, baby.
Don't be mean.
Come on.
(VAULT SCANNER BEEPING)
(VAULT UNLOCKING)
(SIGHING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
"For Rosa and Nico.
See you soon,
- Uncle Dom"
MONACO
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
You sure about this?
You know I am.
You don't need to do this.
Just leave me alone.
Bro, I'm not trying
to be negative,
but casinos
are the kinds of places
designed to take money
from guys like you and me.
When I win here
I'm buying you a lifetime
supply of antidepressants.
You don't put
ten million on red!
Enough already.
You put it on black.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
No more bets.
Right this way, my dear.
You stay right here,
I'll be right back.
So, this is
your dream, huh?
It's enough for me, man.
I take it that's
your dream.
Absolutely. What up, boy?
What's going on?
You good?
Yes, yes.
You know what's crazy?
There's only four
of those cars
in the whole world.
Yeah, I got the only one
in the Western Hemisphere.
I made a sheikh
in Abu Dhabi an offer
he could not refuse.
Huh. That's a nice
lady you got there, too.
Absolutely.
What's happening?
(LAUGHING)
We got to go, man.
Let's do this.
Okay, I'll drive.
In that?
Come on, man,
no way.
No, no. Not in this.
In that.
Are you serious right now?
Man, this is crazy!
Yes, I guess that means
there are two in the
Western Hemisphere, huh?
What's your smart ass
got to say now?
You know what?
We can always
shine together, baby.
Get dressed, man,
we got things to do!
So, where to now?
I don't know.
Never been to Madrid.
I thought you wanted
to go to Tokyo.
We'll get there.
Eventually.
BRIAN: Nice surprise.
Crazy, right?
This is the happiest
I've ever seen my sister.
It's because we're free.
You know,
I want another shot.
Yeah?
Yeah.
No wagers, nobody else.
Just you and me,
once and for all.
You sure you can handle
the disappointment?
Are you?
All right, O'Conner.
Let's see what you got.
DIPLOMATIC SECURITY
SERVICE HEADQUARTERS -
WASHINGTON, D.C.
(TYPING)
You need to look at that.
Berlin, 3:00 a.m.
This morning.
A team of drivers
hijacked a military convoy.
Toretto?
Nope.
I ain't interested.
Yes, you are.
Keep looking.
Do you believe in ghosts?
THE MOTOR VEHICLE ACTION
SEQUENCES DEPICTED
IN THIS FILM ARE DANGEROUS.
ALL STUNTS WERE PERFORMED
IN CONTROLLED ENVIRONMENTS
WITH PROFESSIONALLY TRAINED
STUNT CREWS ON CLOSED ROADS.
NO ATTEMPTS SHOULD BE MADE
TO DUPLICATE ANY ACTION,
DRIVING OR CAR PLAY SCENES
HEREIN PORTRAYED.