That's the cleanup
crew up on the track,
and that's a lot of racers
involved there, folks.
Jack, you realize you got
this in the bag, right?
Season's wrapped up, man.
Doesn't matter where you place.
I'm telling you,
I got intermittent miss.
- Last two laps.
- On it!
Get those plug wires!
Jakob! Now.
Hey, Pop.
Tell me what you see, Dom.
Got an oil spill
going into turn two.
Bell's driving safe.
Corbin's got a sponsor in the stands,
so he's pushing it.
Talking about me?
You got a real problem
with car 23.
- Linder.
- About to whip your ass, Toretto!
- Settle down, pretty boy!
- That's right. Yeah, you.
- Shut up!
- You want to tell your driver
- he's gonna get somebody hurt?
- What'd you say?
- Hey! Leave it!
- Go home! You suck!
He's just pissed
I got that spot
in the Busch Series
next season, not him.
Life's got no shortage of guys
like Kenny Linder.
You're good!
It's not about being
the stronger man, Dom.
It's about being
the bigger one.
I swear to God, this guy.
Pop, turn two, turn two!
Got it. I'm walking him in.
Shit!
Tell me what you see, Dom.
He's gonna
come at you for that.
Get ready on your left.
Three-eighths ratchet.
Three-eighths driver.
Six-inch extension.
Are you sure?
Remember what your
daddy told you.
Be precise in life.
It can make all the difference.
Now, watch this.
See how it's working now?
And you see
what's happening?
It's turning the screw.
You're right.
Water heater's out again.
It's the price we pay
for peace and quiet.
Want to come
and give us a hand?
Are you expecting someone?
Brian, remember
what we practiced.
Yo, yo!
We come in peace.
We come in peace!
It's me!
Roman? Maybe you
don't recognize me
'cause I've been tanning
all week, bro.
B, come out, son.
What you gonna do
with that thing, man?
What, you out here trying to
kill elephants or something?
We would've
called first.
Except you actually need phones
in order to get phone calls.
You know that, right?
- Little B!
- Hi.
Wow.
You're so big. Hi.
Now, I know you don't carpool.
So what's up?
Mayday! Mayday!
My plane is under attack
by a rogue agent!
We're being boarded.
I've got dangerous cargo on board.
I need you to assemble the team.
...still alive.
I'll explain...
It's an SOS transmission
from Mr. Nobody's plane.
It came through with
a mess of encrypted data,
most of which
I'm still trying to crack.
- Did anybody else get this?
- Well, that's the thing.
He sent it only to us.
Why just us?
He caught Cipher.
But there was a midair attack,
and she was extracted.
It seems his plane crashed
somewhere here,
over the northwest region
of Montequinto.
If Mr. Nobody survived,
we need to find him.
But the whole area's
sealed off.
Isolationist, run by military.
We're not on call anymore.
Wait, wait.
Dom, this is Cipher.
The woman who killed
the mother of your child.
Things change.
Listen, we're wheels up
at 8:00 a.m.
if you change your mind.
Thank you.
Daddy,
do you know where God is?
- Where is God?
- In your heart.
He's in your heart, too.
And you know something?
I'll always be in your heart.
Hey, little guy.
I have a gift for you.
Your father
gave this to me.
And now I'm gonna
give it to you.
It's very special.
Take care of it.
Good night.
This isn't who we are.
Brian and Mia got out of the game
when they became parents.
We're not them.
...under attack by a rogue agent!
We're being boarded.
I've got dangerous cargo on board.
...assemble the team.
...still alive.
I'll explain...
Mia, it's Dom.
I need a favor.
You know, I would love to see my nephew
just a little bit more often
than, say,
world-ending emergencies
- and holidays, once in a while, maybe.
- Okay.
And how's the buster?
He's good.
He's really good.
You know,
now that I'm a father,
I can't stop thinking
about our dad.
And, uh...
What life would have
been like if he was alive.
We'd be a very different people,
don't you think?
Dom, what's happened?
Something I hope
I'm wrong about.
Coming up on the signal,
two miles
It's deep in the militarized
zone of Montequinto.
- I hope everyone's ready.
- Ready?
Y'all want to make jokes
about me not making practical decisions?
This is as prepared
as it gets.
We all see you, man.
Nobody thinks you're
compensating for anything.
- I'll take point.
- Careful.
Careful's when you get hurt.
Right now, we have a ten-minute
window between patrols.
Mr. Nobody's signal is close,
but we've got to move quickly, guys.
We do not want to cross paths
with the military here.
- It's inside.
- Cover us.
The source of the SOS signal is coming
from inside this thing.
Somebody wanted in.
Plane must have gone down before
they could cut through.
Or it was sent down on purpose
to stop 'em.
Yeah, well, their mistake
was trying to cut into it.
But just give me a minute.
I can get in.
Dom.
There's not
a soul in sight.
No sign of Mr. Nobody.
Got it.
What the hell is this?
Whatever it is,
Mr. Nobody wanted us to find it.
How's that work...
Go!
What? You don't know who I am?
You think I'm scared?
Roman, where the hell
are you?
Who's compensating now, Tej?
"Peligro minas."
What does that mean?
Tej, how fast we got
to go to clear 'em?
Please don't tell me
you're thinking
- what I think you're thinking.
- Why?
What does
"peligro minas" mean?
- Tej, how fast?
- I don't know, man.
Somebody answer me!
What does
"peligro minas" mean?
"Peligro minas" means
"danger, land mines"!
What?
How fast, Tej?
Assuming
a 50-foot blast radius
and a half a second trigger
delay, I'd say about 80.
I can't!
My speedometer only goes up to 70.
What do I do?
You put your foot
to that floor,
and you pray!
Get to that palm plantation,
and then we're clear.
Whoa!
Roman, you good?
My ass is en fuego!
Tej! Wait! Land mine!
How in the hell
are you not dead?
I'm fine.
Wait, okay, I think
I found us another way out.
Two miles to what looks like
a bridge across the border.
Good. The sooner we get out of here,
the better.
Letty, on the right.
The device.
Get in.
That was Jakob back there,
wasn't it?
- Always check your mirrors, bitches!
- Oh, my God.
Oh, hell no.
Are we supposed
to drive across that?
Well, I said
it looked like a bridge.
Oh, my God!
The military's not giving up.
We got to get
past the border.
Where's the bridge?
No. No, no.
Dom.
Well, that was new.
Look, we're in the clear.
But this thing is a mess.
The headlines out there?
Secret spy plane
crashes in a hostile country?
Followed by some kind
of covert ops firefight?
I'll get you where you need,
and then I'm gonna need
to back off.
I appreciate the favor.
I got to stop
doing so many favors.
What we doing, Ramsey?
Like, where are we going?
I was able
to decrypt the data
that came through
with Mr. Nobody's SOS,
and I found
GPS coordinates,
definitely included
on purpose.
You knew about Jakob?
Question.
Who is Jakob?
Jakob is,
or was, Dom's brother.
Oh, my... My bad.
I'm sorry.
I'm just processing.
Brother?
You got a brother?
Who also happens to be
some kind of super spy
with his own private army,
who drives literally
like a bat out of hell,
who preplanned an aerial jump
and landed
at the bottom of an airplane?
Who does that?
A Toretto.
That's my dad!
He's gone! He's gone!
We got to get him
out of there.
We got to get him out of there!
That's my dad!
That's my dad! That's my dad!
Get him out of there!
That's my dad!
There's a couple of release
forms we've got to sign.
Few clearances.
Everything else is down there
around the corner.
Hey.
Nobody's supposed
to be around here.
You Toretto's other son?
You're the useless one, right?
What is that?
Get out of here. Go.
So a man can't pay
his last respects?
That's what that is?
No.
No, not you.
You're the one that killed him.
No, racing killed him.
Look, he knew that I was gonna
pit him into the wall. He knew that.
Now, I don't know if he dropped gear.
I don't know.
I swear... I swear to God,
- if you don't get out of here...
- What? What?
Go find Buddy.
Now!
Oh.
All right, well,
now we got the golden boy.
Leave.
You here
to make threats, too?
"Leave" is a simple word.
Man, what is it
with you Torettos
where you're all the heroes
in your own stories?
Look, I'm gonna
tell you a secret.
You, your dad, me,
we're all stuck,
going round and round
in the same shitty circle.
And we ain't
never getting out.
You ain't half the man
my dad was.
- At least I'm alive, asshole.
- What did you say?
Get off me!
Dom! Dom!
Dom!
Dom, no! Dom!
No, man!
In here.
Jakob.
I simply cannot believe that
magnet trick actually worked.
It looked so damn cool.
Look at this here.
I got this off
the cockpit feed.
Oh, I love being rich.
It was sloppy.
He almost had me.
- She say anything?
- Nope. Nada.
You know, I look at her
and I feel creeped out.
And sort of turned on
at the same time.
Is that weird?
Nice operation.
You snatched me off
Mr. Nobody's plane midair
without a scratch,
and you took him down.
Money well spent.
- Do you know who I am?
- I know who you are.
Do you?
East L.A. is a tough enough
place to grow up.
But it was your brother's shadow
that turned you into this.
Isn't it?
So your whole life,
you pushed yourself to be faster than Dom.
Smarter than Dom.
Stronger than Dom.
Tell me, do you hate him
enough that it keeps you up at night?
Still?
All these years later?
I should've just hired you
instead of coercing your brother
a couple of years back.
I don't work
for the competition.
That's cute.
You thinking
you're the competition.
Says the woman in the box.
Look familiar?
The other half's hidden
in one of the agency's thousands of vaults.
I need you
to find out which one.
We secured the master drive here
from Mr. Nobody's plane.
The rest of the hardware
is a bit dated.
Pre-Internet.
To make sure you don't go hack
into anything we don't want you to.
Say you get what you're after.
A weapon so dangerous
it shouldn't exist for another half century.
What would you do with it?
Launch some
global attack?
Sell it to the
highest bidder?
Or maybe you see yourself
as a necessary
shock to the system.
I bet all you ever wanted
was a hug.
You read my psych eval.
Good for you.
I read your
second-grade report card.
That's what I do.
Your chin,
it's distinctive.
I know the Torettos have
quite the mixed bloodlines,
but I never detected
a Nordic strain.
Finding the two halves
of Project Aries is the easy part.
Add in your brother Dom
to the mix?
You don't have a chance.
Plans are in motion.
Qasar Khan.
What?
Genghis Khan's little brother.
Nobody's heard of him either.
Talk about off the grid.
I don't think they had grids
when this place was built.
If a Ninja Turtle pop out on me,
tell you right now, I'm out.
No way this place
was sanctioned by the agency.
This was definitely
Mr. Nobody's secret hideout.
What now, Dom?
Whoever Jakob has become...
...and whatever he's up to...
...it's on me,
- and me alone.
- Nah.
Whatever's on you,
it's on us.
Let's get to work.
That's a rotary phone.
Yes. Thank you.
I know what a rotary dial phone is.
Okay. Well, what's that?
It's a JX1000
reel-to-reel tape recorder.
What about that?
It's a GB Industries
4K telex machine.
Impressive.
What about these?
They're floppy disks.
And that's
a Rafutek micro recorder,
that's a Smithson
autoprinter,
and that thing there
is an Omaha 3010 fax machine.
It's like e-mail,
- but wasteful.
- Mmm.
Are we done here?
Did I pass your little test?
What's your mamma's
phone number?
Right.
Y'all ever thought about
how many wild missions we've been on?
How we somehow
always survive?
Yeah.
So far, so good, I guess.
It's just luck.
No, no, no, see,
y'all not listening.
Think about this.
We've now been on insane
missions around the world,
doing what most would say
is damn near impossible.
And I ain't got
one single scar to show for it?
I mean, look at my jacket.
Those are bullet holes from 14 dudes
trying to take my head
clean off its shoulders.
We've taken out cars,
trains, tanks.
I'm not gonna even mention
the submarine.
And yet we're still here.
Exactly.
Ramsey, what happens
when you test a theory
over and over again only to come
to the same result?
A hypothesis becomes fact.
But you're not actually suggesting that...
I don't know, but when
the improbable happens again and again,
that's more than luck.
Maybe we're not so normal.
That's what I'm saying.
We are not normal.
Okay, um, just to clarify,
are you two maybe suggesting
that we're, what,
invincible?
- Maybe.
Or maybe
you're just a dumbass.
Take your dumbass jacket
with you, man.
Pretty impressive driving
out there.
You miss the old life.
Do you?
Every day.
Guys.
We got a little company.
Think you know this person.
- It's so good to see you.
- I missed you.
Thank you.
Of course.
You should've told me.
She deserved to know.
Jakob's my brother, too.
I need to be here.
You get involved here,
you put everything you have at risk.
Your kids and the whole world
that you built.
We're all risking something.
Dom, listen to me.
My kids and yours are in
the safest hands possible.
With Brian.
Our world's grown, Dom.
I got this one.
Guys!
Guys. Get over here.
You gotta come see this.
Don't ever say Roman
ain't look out for y'all.
Huh?
Yeah. You get a stack.
And you get a stack.
And Roman gets...
Roman, this cash
is from Yugoslavia.
Yugoslavia hasn't been
a country since 1992.
What, you a expert
on history now?
No, no, no.
I'm an expert on cash.
USD. Huh?
Yeah.
Professor Dumbass.
I just need to find me some luggage
so I can put all this in.
The firewall on this old thing
is actually pretty good.
But, you know, port scan,
UDP message peek,
pop to root shell, and...
...say hello to Project Aries.
What is it?
It's what we got
from Mr. Nobody's plane.
Or at least
part of it.
Aries was designed to override
and assimilate anything that runs on code.
Any computer anywhere.
If it operates on zeros and ones,
it's vulnerable.
Aries can own it.
It can
weaponize anything.
Someone could
burn your house down
with your refrigerator
if they wanted to.
Oh, so, now my refrigerator's
gonna kill me?
It could be made to.
How about my George Foreman Grill
or foot massager?
Y'all...
Do you know how it feels to create
something that could end the world?
No.
Well, I do.
And this will.
If you take Aries
and upload it to a satellite,
it'll spread like a virus.
Then it'll be a matter of time
before someone can control
any weapon system, traditional, nuclear,
stuff we haven't even seen yet,
and just point it
wherever they want.
Jakob reboots
the world order within minutes.
Ares is
the god of war, right?
If Jakob gets his hands
on this,
he'll be the god
of damn near everything.
Because of how
dangerous it was,
the Aries prototype was recovered
and split into two halves by Mr. Nobody.
Both of which are worthless
without the activation key.
Jakob now has
one of the pieces.
He'll be going
after the other half next.
As for the key, it's...
It's vanished.
So, we find it.
If we're gonna beat
Jakob to it,
we're gonna
have to split up.
Roman, Tej, I know a couple of guys
operating out of Germany
that could get us
anything we need.
- I'm on it.
- Wait, there's one more thing.
Mr. Nobody's transmission had
one name connected to the key.
You guys are gonna want
to brace yourselves for this.
No way.
That's exactly
what I said.
So you're saying Han's death
is connected to all of this?
He has to have
something to do with it.
I'll look into it.
Tej, can you send me
all the files you have on Han?
- Yeah.
- I'll go with you.
Letty.
I got this the day Han died.
Mexico.
Check the postmark.
Whatever he was up to,
it ended here.
Tokyo.
What are you gonna do
about Jakob?
I'm gonna find him.
How?
An old friend.
Yo, what do you think?
It doesn't matter.
It's all about how
you choose to see it.
Shit.
I told you I was right.
- I'm Leo.
- Santos.
Dom. What are you guys in for?
Driving while brown.
You see that?
Hairline crack
in the fuel line.
Air gets in there,
you got a lean condition.
Lean condition?
I got a taste for wasting
and tasting the blood
Murder, I heard her
when she screamed and dropped
'Cause her son caught the slug
Relate this to no choice
And listen to this
s traight-up man
Before they ban the voice
While I rhyme
to the rhythm o f a pop
Remember the first brother
to run
Is the first to get shot
Whoever said
that what I say
And portray is negativity
Need to come kick it
in the city with me
And find the black and crack
in fact, they take that back
Because they really can't
deal with that...
Hey.
You had another
eight months.
Good behavior.
Oh, Dom.
You didn't call.
I would have
picked you up.
I'm here now.
Welcome home,
brother.
Come here.
Yeah! Yeah, Jakob!
Whoo!
That's what
I'm talking about!
How you doin'?
Who wants next?
I said, who wants next?
I got next.
Dom.
Well, when'd you get out, man?
I said I got next.
Come on, Dom.
You don't want to race me
in Buddy's old Charger.
No, it won't even be close.
My Mustang?
With all the mods that I put in it?
Car don't make the driver.
Here's how this goes.
You win,
you come back home.
You lose,
you keep driving,
you don't stop,
you don't ever come back.
Ever.
What do you mean, Dom?
I know what you did.
The day we lost him,
Dad kept talking about a misfire.
Remember?
You were the last one
under his hood that day.
A minute later, he was gone.
Tell me
why you killed Dad.
Now let's race.
Armed robbery in Echo Park.
Fourth Street Bridge is open.
Clear, clear, clear!
Ready?
Set.
Go.
Set the time
for the battleground
Guided missiles
will hunt you down
Drones surrounding your home
Don't breathe, you're not
safe underground
Political landscape shape
has been polarized
Now it's time
to reveal the zeal
Everybody breathe,
get mobilized
Trying to buy
the American dream
But it's overpriced
Five-bil deal
for the fighterjets
Being shipped
to the Middle East
It'll cost ten billion
more dollars
For neighbors to feel safe
to breathe
What, what
- What, what
- Breathe with me
What
Sometimes we got to stop
and breathe
Stop, breathe
Breathe with me
Sometimes we got to stop
and breathe
Too soon.
No!
Green light,
we gon' ride the night
Loud pipes,
Fishtailing out
the parking lot
No cops,
we ain't gonna stop
Switch gears,
we gon' drag and drift
Hit the gas
and we pack the clip
Muscle cars sound mad
as hell
- Whoa, whoa
- Na-na-na, whoa
- Na-na-na, whoa.
...and beating the shortstop.
Line drive
over the head of Gonzalez
on the field for a base hit.
Up next...
Place still
looks the same.
Just like
your dad left it.
I'm looking for Jakob.
Can't help you, man.
I know you took Jakob in
after my father died.
The worst thing
you can do to a Toretto
is take away their family.
That's what you did to Jakob.
You've got people
who love you,
count on you,
care for you.
He ain't got no one.
You get in his way,
this ain't gonna end
until one of you guys are in the ground.
I know you did the best
you could, Buddy.
But we both know
he's about to cause a lot of hurt.
I did my best
to take care of Jakob.
But I'm no Jack Toretto.
You've got to make peace
with the past if you...
If you want hope
for the future.
He's in London.
That's all I know.
Dom.
I hope you find your peace.
The chance for peace died
that day on the track.
Han's old shop.
God! It looks like this place has been
picked over a thousand times.
- Gotta start somewhere.
- It doesn't make any sense.
I mean,
Han ends up in Tokyo
and he's supposed
to have something to do with the key?
But police records
make it sound like
he was running around
with a bunch of small time crooks.
Don't mock it.
That's how we started.
Maybe Han was looking
for a change of scenery
after Gisele died.
People mourn
in different ways.
Letty, how did Mr. Nobody
get connected with Han?
And they never...
They never
crossed paths unless...
Gisele.
She's former Mossad.
Mr. Nobody is a spy.
They could have run
in the same circles.
There's Mossad clearance
all over the files Mr. Nobody had on Han.
Mission spikes
going back to Mexico,
which is where Gisele was working
when she met Dom and Brian.
Gisele's gotta be the link.
Leave it to Mr. Nobody
to confuse everyone.
This place is a dead end.
Let's get out of here.
I'll check in with
Tej and Roman.
I'm a lane switcher
Big tank, bank filler
Real killer,
die for my gang member
Gun driller,
dope man dope dealer
Gorilla, bang, bang,
lane switcher...
She's ready to roll.
No. No!
No, Sean!
Tell me you are not modding
the quick disconnect valve on the LOX line.
Hey, man, chill out.
All right? It's all good.
- That tweak just saved us 0.4 seconds.
- "All good"?
This isn't Top Gun, Maverick.
You don't follow
the rules here, you die.
Hey, come on.
That's a bit much.
When you know what too much pressure
in the LOX line can do,
come talk to me.
Till then, stay in your lane.
Yo, you're lucky
to even be in my lane.
In case you forgot,
I'm the one that figured out
how to let us build
rocket engines and get paid.
This whole thing was my idea.
So who are you gonna trust
with your brilliant idea,
this glorified mechanic
or a rocket scientist?
Without me,
you'd be working at Jiffy Lube.
Guys, guys.
Look, it's all good.
Who cares about
who did what?
Kind of hard
for you to do anything
when you pee your pants
every time you fly, Twinkie.
Did I hear that right?
You a runner
and you afraid of flying?
"Twinkie"?
So, you must be Ding Dong
and Sno Ball.
- Right?
- Yo... Uh-uh.
I don't go
by that name anymore.
You went by
that name ever?
Like, ever?
I... That's...
- Hey! We're up.
- Oh, good.
Hey, fellas.
Y'all seen ten-second cars?
Well, say hello
to the two-second car.
Is that a Pontiac Fiero
strapped to
a rocket engine?
Impressive, I know.
No.
No, that's not impressive.
Eyes up! Here it comes!
Let the race begin!
Plane's taking off!
Go, go, go, go!
Yes!
We did it!
Uh...
I'm confused.
Y'all didn't actually
beat the jet.
It didn't explode.
- Yeah, or melt.
- Yeah.
She's still
in one piece.
You mean "pieces"?
Hey, Jiffy Lube, next time,
will you listen to me?
Look, we heard
y'all could get us some wheels.
Preferably the kind
that don't explode.
Is that possible?
Well, the Honda dealership's
about 3,000 miles that way.
Dominic Toretto sent us.
Who's Dominic Toretto?
Arigato.
This place is a dead end.
Do you think Jakob could be
onto the Han connection?
If he has all the information
we do, probably.
I never told Dom,
I stayed in touch with him
for a while after what happened.
He was over at Buddy's
for about a year, and then
he was gone,
with a message not to follow.
But after he disappeared,
I was so desperate to find him
that I would've...
Would've done anything.
I even broke into a police archive,
but I didn't find anything.
You what?
You were, like, 16.
I did what I had to do.
Yeah.
How about you?
How are you doing?
It's a change of pace, huh?
Just as I was remembering...
...who I was,
everything changed.
It slowed down.
There's peace for me
in the chaos.
It's like I... I need to face the world
head-on or something to feel alive.
Seeing Little Brian
hiding in a hole because we had
unexpected company
that got to me.
We never used to hide.
Hey, Dom's my brother,
but you will always be my sister.
Funny how we all have secrets.
What?
You got to be kidding me.
What is it?
Remember what Han
used to say about Tokyo?
You mean how,
in all the old Westerns,
cowboys would make a run for the border
to get away from the law,
how Tokyo was his...
Mexico.
No way.
Hmm.
Nice necklace,
Queenie.
Diamonds and emeralds
never looked so good.
Dominic Toretto.
The word on the street
is you got locked up.
Yeah, well, in and out,
you know.
When are they gonna learn
some birds
can't be caged?
Are you looking
for one of me sons?
Not tonight.
You do the driving,
I'll cut you in for 15%.
My thieving days are over.
Mine ain't.
You coming?
I'm looking for someone.
Would've shown up in town
a little while ago.
A lot of guys,
a lot of resources.
Oh, yeah, yeah, word did go round
on a crew that just turned up,
led by an American.
Yeah, he bought some arms
off a local seller.
Rumor had it he was
into something big up in Edinburgh.
Local seller, huh?
She wouldn't happen to be wearing
a stolen necklace, would she?
He paid well. What was I
supposed to do?
This geezer was about
your height, actually.
Similar features.
Oh, bloody hell, he's not your cousin
or something, is he?
He's my brother.
Get the hand brake for me,
would you, darling?
Glad I'm not the only one
with a family full of eccentrics.
He offered payment
for something else.
You.
I am the thorn in your crown
Veneno you hold in your mouth
That you won't spit out
You know, nothing's
more powerful than the love of family.
But you turn that
into anger and resentment,
nothing's more dangerous.
Dom?
Don't get yourself
killed, okay?
You're my favorite American.
Dominic Toretto.
Tell me.
Why is the best fruit
always forbidden?
You should know.
Mmm.
This is your kind of party,
isn't it, Dom?
Beautiful women, best cars,
best everything.
You know,
best security, too.
I'm Otto. I'm your
brother's partner.
Well, financier.
But, you know, my dad,
he's a dictator,
so we're not talking
regular people rich here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Everything you see here, I own.
These girls, if you want
to meet one of them,
maybe two, maybe three, just let me know.
They're on the payroll.
I offer a bomb-ass
dental plan, too. Huh?
Where is Jakob?
He's inside.
The brother
you're looking for,
he's from an old life.
He's long gone.
All I see is the same scared little kid
that killed our father.
That's your mistake.
The spy game,
this is my world.
What do you think
happened, Dom,
every time you
took somebody down?
Their territory just
stayed crime-free?
The Trans, Braga...
The Shaws...
Cipher.
You paved the way for me.
So here's my offer.
It's the same one you gave me.
You leave.
Now.
You drive away,
and you never come back.
Ever.
A deal?
I showed you mercy!
And I won't show it
to you again.
Toretto.
Since my dad
is head of state,
it makes me
a foreign dignitary
and this place
an embassy.
Which means you just trespassed
into my country and attempted murder.
So, naturally, I called in a little favor
with all my good friends from INTERPOL.
You keep digging around
in the past, Dom,
you're not gonna like
what you find.
And here I thought my dad
was a pain in the ass.
But your family
is a train wreck.
Well, now that your brother's
finally out of the game,
it's time
we go to Edinburgh.
Get the second piece,
maybe do a little sightseeing, huh?
Any news on the key?
Don't worry about it.
Our men are closing in.
One week from now,
there won't be a superpower in the world
can take a piss
without our permission.
One week from now, your dad will be
asking you for an allowance.
I'd like that.
Whew.
What's up?
- Well done, Leysa.
- Please.
If it wasn't for you,
I'd still be stealing gas in the D.R.
So Queenie
treating you right?
Like a princesa.
I'm her number-one pick,
you know.
- Cara's little sister done good.
- Good?
You saw my fine ass
in that white dress.
You see how
I been rocking shit?
All this crew,
this is mine. Huh?
I been around the world.
Oh, I almost forgot,
you might need this.
Your boy Jakob biometrics
are encoded to this gun.
You'll have no trouble
tracking him now.
Hey, Letty.
Yeah.
Come look at this.
What the hell?
Han never mentioned
a girl, not ever.
Letty, Mia!
Down, now!
You okay?
Welcome
to St. Giles' Cathedral of Edinburgh.
The High Kirk has a history
stretching back over 900 years.
Renowned for its
stained glass windows,
you can see the intricate
craftsmanship...
We're a go.
Ramsey, talk to me.
What do we got?
I pulled Jakob's biometric
signature off the gun,
and the algorithm I've run
says Jakob's team is right on top of us.
Anywhere between
80 and 100 meters.
Eighty meters?
That's a lot around here.
This whole area
seems pretty packed in.
So, we don't know...
where the secret vault facility
Jakob is looking to hit is,
now, do we?
Wouldn't be a secret
if we did.
You know what?
I'm starting to think
your little English accent
makes you sound
smarter than you are.
Man, can I point out
that a good old-fashioned tracking chip
would've put us within,
like, six feet of this dude?
But, nah, instead,
we out here with biometrics
and facial recognition
imaging.
Feels like we looking for
Where's Waldo in Harry Potter world.
Yeah, uh,
strong argument there,
Tej, but tracking chips
follow the chip.
Before we know it,
we'd be chasing some expensive
yet tacky jacket
to the dry cleaner's.
Biometrics, on the other hand,
are impossible to...
Wait.
Guys, okay,
we have a problem.
Cameras are going down all around us,
and my equipment is freaking out.
What the hell, Jimmy?
Security alert.
Cameras are down.
Damn.
You see anything suspicious?
Uh, where do I start?
First of all, all of this
looks a little spooky.
I even seen these
two ladies walking
with George Washington wigs
on their head from the 1700s.
I feel like I'm in Transylvania
or some damn where.
Ramsey,
we're looking everywhere.
I just grew a new bunion.
This is hopeless.
What?
- You see that?
- See what?
The ears.
They got cauliflower ears.
They fight for a living.
- Don't worry about it.
- Roman.
Hey, man, I ordered
a pair of Crocs.
three weeks ago,
and I'm still waiting!
Where are my shoes, man?
Man, we really need
to work on your planning.
Hey, Dom, you should
get down to the cathedral.
Dumbass here just attacked
some delivery dudes
'cause he didn't like
their ears.
Wait, wait, wait.
How much did you say
you paid for that again?
You know silver
ain't magnetic, right?
You know what? Just shut up.
Just shut up.
Ramsey, say we had a big electromagnet
turned up right around here.
Wouldn't that disrupt
all electronic signals?
Including security systems.
That's it.
That's how Jakob's
getting into the vault.
Guys?
Okay, we've got police
coming from all sides.
- The area's locking down.
- He ain't using roads.
I got eyes on Jakob.
I see Otto.
I'm gonna tail him.
He's heading towards
a blue Jaguar.
Okay, follow him.
Me? I can't.
Why not?
Okay, this is
a bad time to tell you this,
but I don't drive. Okay?
I never got my license.
I don't know how to drive.
And, you know,
no one really drives in London.
Okay? And that is not
my contribution to this group.
It's you or no one.
Shit.
Guys, come on, man.
I feel like, between the six of us,
we can work
this out, right?
Okay. I've got...
Ramsey, shut it off!
Shut it off!
Go, go, go!
Okay.
Brake is on the left,
accelerator right.
Shit.
Hey!
Oh. Sorry!
Whoa!
Oh, no!
Move!
Hey, that was not my fault!
Okay, that one was my fault.
See?
What'd I tell you?
Not even a scratch.
Otto, sending you
new pickup location.
I've got it.
I'm headed to you now.
Otto, where are you?
Jakob, I'm there.
I don't see anybody.
It's because you're
on the wrong street.
That's my car, pal!
Dom!
Go!
Damn it.
You're a natural.
Of course I am.
Okay, listen up!
I want 50 of the best men!
I want guns!
I want wheels,
freaking X-wing fighters, I don't care!
The Millennium Falcon,
Chewbacca if you can get ahold of him.
Money's no object. Go.
Go!
What?
What's so funny?
I...
I was thinking,
if this was a movie,
this would be the moment
where the villain
has an unexpected setback,
overcompensates without
thinking it through
and gets crushed
by the good guys.
No offense, but you have no idea
what we're about to do.
And, for the record,
we're the good guys.
Me? I'm Luke
freaking Skywalker.
Are you sure about that?
I mean, I get
the daddy issues, but...
Look at what you've built.
Really? Luke?
You're right.
No, I'm more of a Han Solo.
No.
You're Yoda.
- Yoda?
- Mm-hmm.
No. The little green guy?
- Yeah.
- No.
Ah, shit, I'll take it.
Because he's
a powerful Jedi, right?
No.
Yoda's a puppet.
With someone's hand
up his ass.
So, what now, Dom?
No one outruns their past.
And yours just
caught up to you.
Man.
There is literally zero industrial
or weapons-grade electromagnets
I can find that
are this powerful.
Look at the pull strength
level here.
- It's crazy.
- Yeah.
Wait, watch this.
Every time.
I can't believe it.
What are you doing, bruh?
I'm hungry.
- Hey, guys.
- Oh, damn.
Surprise.
Nice clubhouse.
'Sup, man?
Nice to meet you.
So you got
my postcard, huh?
Little B.
Yes, it's daddy.
How you doin'?
Stayin' out of trouble?
Of course not.
Well, at least you're honest.
And that's the most
important thing.
Oh, I miss you
so much more.
And I'm coming home soon.
How's...
I'll tell you what, if I'm not home
by the time you count till 1,000,
you tell Uncle Brian
that I said you could have
a second treat before dinner.
It's a promise.
And I always keep my promises.
I'm just still trying
to figure out...
How are you still alive?
Well, after
Gisele died...
...I didn't know what to do.
I was aimless.
- Lost.
- Absolutely.
But can you get
to the part where
the car exploded
and you're still alive?
- Like, I'm trying to...
- Roman, can you...
Can you just be quiet
for one minute?
We made plans.
We had dreams.
So what's our next
adventure after this?
How about we stay
in one place?
Where are you thinking?
Tokyo.
We always talk
about Tokyo.
Tokyo it is.
You know, it's funny,
Gisele led me there,
and I wasn't even
looking for it.
But it became home.
Then, one day,
Mr. Nobody came calling.
I worked with Gisele.
Back when I was
a CIA operative
running the drug trade
in Central America.
The good old days.
Gisele was my best.
You can lose an asset
at any time.
Bullet, knife, wire.
But I never thought
I'd lose her...
...to love.
What do you want?
I'm offering you a job, Han.
Here, in Tokyo.
Why me?
'Cause I saw your work
with Gisele.
I saw that
she trusted you.
And that means
I can trust you.
And that is very rare
in this line of work.
And all I knew was that
I had to steal some tech
from the home
of a scientist couple.
But, as usual,
Mr. Nobody didn't tell me
everything.
In fact, he left out
the most important part.
I was 11.
My parents would take me
to the movies on Saturdays
if I tried hard in school
during the week.
I was so excited to go
I forgot my raincoat,
so I went back in.
At first, I didn't see it.
By the time I looked out
the window...
...Mom and Dad were gone.
Turns out I wasn't
the only one looking for this thing.
Get down!
Han saved me.
Wouldn't leave me behind.
He knew I'd always
be a target,
so he taught me
how to survive.
We became a family.
"Always be a target"?
Why?
'Cause she is the key.
Everybody's been looking
for a thing.
It was a person all along.
My parents didn't want
Project Aries to fall into the wrong hands,
so they locked it with their own DNA,
something we share.
And then, one day,
Mr. Nobody gave me the heads-up
that one of his best agents
went rogue.
So when Deckard Shaw
came calling,
we used it as cover.
But you got killed
in a car crash, Han.
Mr. Nobody had a way
of making things look real.
Pretty nifty magic trick.
Yeah, I've done better.
Now for the hard part.
Keeping you dead.
My death...
...became the best way
to stay alive.
- What's happening?
- It's some kind of hidden subroutine
the system follows.
That's it, right there.
Yeah, nobody moves,
everybody lives.
Jakob.
I'm sorry, Mia.
I was the rogue agent.
Me.
Dom, you ever think about
how Mr. Nobody found you?
Think he just dropped out
of the sky and chose you?
I ran missions with Mr. Nobody
out of this place for years.
I've been looking for that key
for a long time, Dom.
And you just
handed her over.
I told you.
This is my world.
Got it.
Got a lot of guys here.
You trust 'em?
Trust this.
You know the only good thing
to come from Dad dying?
If he hadn't, I'd have spent
my entire life in your shadow.
And now you're gonna
spend the rest of yours living in mine.
Only good thing
about Dad dying...
...was he didn't have to watch
what you became.
You never deserved
the Toretto name.
You think
you knew Dad, huh?
What, 'cause you were his favorite?
You don't know shit!
Okay?
You want the truth?
Dad died 'cause he was
trying to throw that race.
We were in deep debt.
'Cause of how
he felt about you,
he had to ask me
for help.
How was I supposed to know
that car was gonna blow?
A good son would've said no.
And a real brother
would've come to me.
Come to you?
He made me promise
you would never find out.
And through all of it...
...I kept that promise.
The girl comes
with me.
Jakob!
I will stop you.
And that's my promise.
Hey!
Sue. Sue. Ah.
Come on. Come on.
Down!
Go! Go!
Come on!
This way!
I'm always here.
Tell him.
No!
Dom.
Tell me what you see, son.
See, cars like this
are immortal.
'70 Chargers
are designed so well
that if you take care
of 'em,
they'll run for 100 years.
Immortal?
Just like a family, Dom.
Build it right,
you take care of it...
...it'll live beyond you.
Daddy.
Little B.
When are you coming home?
Come...
No. You know I'm good for it.
I promise I'll deliver.
I'm telling you,
I got intermittent miss.
- Last two laps.
- On it!
Get those plug wires!
Jakob! Now.
You're good!
No!
You came for me, Letty.
None of it is worth a thing
if I lose you.
Do you hear me?
Is this who we are?
Yeah.
From here,
things move quickly.
Jakob has all the pieces
he needs.
Once he activates Aries,
all he needs to do
is send the signal global.
And then there's
no stopping him, ever.
He'll have to launch
some kind of pirate satellite,
something that'll act
as an amplifier,
infecting other satellites
in orbit one by one.
So we find him, stop him,
and then we get Elle back.
Our odds are
zero here, Han.
Satellite equipment
is easy enough to track,
but we're not gonna
beat Jakob to a launch.
Which gives us
a two-target problem:
Jakob on the ground...
With his own private army.
- And the satellite.
- Which can't be hacked.
Not remotely.
We'd have to do it
physically,
Fifty miles above ground
while the satellite is in orbit.
Orbit?
We need help.
Otherwise, we have no chance.
We do it ourselves.
It's where we've been
that got us this far.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Do y'all not understand?
Clearly, y'all don't.
Because if you did,
you'd be pissing your pants
like a normal person.
Orbit.
That's outer space.
That's another level.
What we gonna do?
Hijack a space shuttle?
Put rockets on our backs?
That's exactly what
we're gonna do.
What?
There goes my father's diplomatic ties
with Eastern Europe.
This place is going to be crawling
with every cop in the city.
Time to get the hell
out of here.
Keep her close.
It's activated.
As soon as the satellite reaches orbit,
we start the uplink.
Oh, damn.
What?
You see that?
We can't have
an air leak, man.
Are you really patching
yourself up with duct tape?
Yes.
I don't know
if you've noticed or not,
but this whole operation
is Band-Aids and duct tape.
Man, this is insane.
We are headed
to outer space.
You acting like we on our way
to Home Depot.
This is ridiculous, man.
I'm about to abort this whole mission
and take my Black ass home.
We're literally gonna be
in a perpetual freefall.
Freefall?
What does that
even mean?
Roman, it means
numbers don't lie.
As long as we obey
the laws of physics,
then we'll be fine, okay?
It's just all
math and science.
I knew I should've
listened to my teachers.
Four minutes to launch.
You fellas good to go?
Yeah, we just up here
putting a bunch of duct tape on shit.
You know,
that's what Tej do.
Man, please hurry up
so I can stop hearing his damn mouth.
- Yes, we're good to go.
- We're not good.
This is the same car
that we watched
do a test run and explode.
This is not smart, Tej.
Don't worry, man.
With my ceramic polymer coating,
you're gonna be just fine.
You're 100% fireproof.
Exactly.
All eight thrusters
fully functional.
Hey, please don't tell me
you're still running launch simulations.
Virgin Galactic launched
at 36,000 feet.
The space shuttle tests
around 50,000 feet.
Our last test run with this load means
we'll have to go higher,
way higher!
If we don't get them
high enough,
these guys are
gonna be pancakes at IHOP
before the coffee
even gets to the table.
Hey! We can still hear you!
Don't worry, guys.
We got this.
We do got this, right?
I've run thermal imaging.
Elle's in the armory truck.
And I've got a lock
on the Aries signal.
It's coming from
the beast up ahead.
We need to get in there
to deactivate it
by the time Roman
and Tej are in position.
Ramsey, power us up.
Satellite is in low orbit.
Begin.
All right,
we're passing 50,000 feet!
Time to get ready, boys.
What we supposed
to be doing
with these old-ass suits
that ain't been used
since World War I?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Astronauts R Us
was closed for shopping today.
Listen, these suits
are just like space suits.
They both account
for pressure differential.
Only thing is we may
blow up like balloons just a little bit.
- That's the only difference.
- What?
We just hit
the launch altitude.
- You guys ready for a five count?
- No, man!
I'm barely ready to go scuba diving
in this old-ass thing.
Don't listen to him.
We ready!
- "We"?
- Yes, I said "we"!
I thought you
was invincible.
Let's see how invincible
your Black ass is after this.
- Punch it!
- No! Tej!
Oh, my God!
I don't want to die!
Ignition!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
We're in outer space!
Told you numbers don't lie.
This is crazy, bro!
Man, how much candy
did you eat?
Well, I... I eat candy
when I get nervous.
If you shart in this Fiero,
I swear to...
Really? Really, Tej?
I thought you said
you took care of this.
Yeah. Hey.
You take them back
to the freaking junkyard right now!
All right, Han, Mia,
you're up!
Now.
Letty.
Han!
Not all of us.
Now, the satellite we looking
for should be somewhere...
There.
Right there.
You see it?
Got it.
Tell me you know
how to work the thrusters.
Tej, numbers is
what you do, right?
Driving is what I do.
Two dudes from the ghetto,
outer space.
You know ain't nobody
gonna believe us, right?
You're right.
Something's wrong
with the satellite array.
It's interfering
with the uplink.
I'll handle it.
Han?
Grab the wheel.
Something's up.
I think I can link
into their feed.
Something you want
to tell me, Otto?
My bad. Satellite uplink
is actually going splendid.
Oh, and, by the way,
I have a new business partner.
Maybe you know her.
Guess who's out
of the box, Jakob.
But I did try to warn you.
You were never my competition.
Otto, there's something
you should know.
Yeah, go on.
Lay it on me, dude.
You're a spoiled rich prick,
and I'm gonna kill you.
Oh, man, I am so sorry.
No one told you, huh?
Spoiled rich pricks
run the world.
Come on. Come on!
Go.
What's happening?
Well, we appear to have lost
our escort and Jakob.
And, well, Dom is making things
a little bit difficult here,
but it's fine.
Really, it's peachy.
Don't worry,
don't worry.
I'll finish this myself.
All right, let's see
what that beast is made of.
You ready, Elle?
Crank it.
If we can't break through,
we stop it.
Guys, that thing
is not slowing down
and the download's
almost done.
Dom, we don't get out of here now,
we're dead.
Letty, drop back and line up
with the front tires.
What?
If we can't slow it
and we can't punch through,
we flip it and we hit
the underside.
Goddamn it!
Why do I have to say this?
Flatten these clowns!
Letty, the wires.
You read my mind.
Han, get in front of me.
Dom, I can't get to you.
But I can.
All right, the satellite
is in range.
Let's power up these magnets
and fry it.
All right, take our time.
Okay. All right.
Tej!
Hold on. Come on, baby.
Power up. Power up.
Shit.
Shit, shit, shit.
What? Talk to me.
What's going on?
The pressure of the launch,
it must have jammed the cables
to the power source.
Damn it, how did
I not think of that?
Guys, where are you?
The upload is almost complete.
Why don't you just kill it?
Let's smash it.
Let's run it over, right?
No. If we crash into that satellite,
we'll probably die.
And even if we don't,
the fuel that it would take to smash it,
we'd be stuck
out here forever.
You got to have faith, bro.
Faith? Faith is not numbers.
You know what, Tej?
You're probably right.
We're not invincible.
We probablyjust been
lucky this whole time.
This might be it.
But you know what?
If we're gonna go out...
...let's go out
on top of the world.
Guys,
what's happening up there?
We've got seconds left.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
We did it.
We did it!
Let's go.
Yes!
Shit.
Not bad, man.
Not bad at all.
Hold on!
Dom!
Yes!
Got to be kidding me.
Shit!
Think these
belong to you.
There's gonna be a lot of people
coming after you, Jake.
Yeah.
This is the world
I chose, Dom.
You know,
Dad wasn't perfect.
But he loved us
all the same.
Someone once gave me
a ten-second car,
as a second chance.
I owe you that,
little brother.
I lost you once.
Don't let that
happen again, okay?
We come in peace!
Hey!
This was the last place
I saw your grandfather.
This is where he raced.
Did you race here, too, Daddy?
No.
But I'll tell you something.
Everything I needed to know about life,
I learned on this track.
You did?
I did.
It's all gonna
be okay, Jakob.
We got some
rough times ahead...
...but it's gonna be okay.
'Cause we're family.
- Fellas.
- Hey.
What?
No way.
What's going on?
I couldn't believe it
when I heard you were alive.
It's a long story.
But, for now,
let's just enjoy the moment, huh?
Guys, this is Elle.
Hey, Elle. I'm Sean.
Just call me T.
- I'm Earl.
- Nice to meet you.
Mia.
Hi. Nice to finally
meet you.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
How much longer
on this food?
Like, I'm...
I'm ready to eat now.
I've been eating
space food for weeks.
Oh, so Tootsie Rolls
are space food?
'Cause that's all
you ate.
It was fat free, bruh.
Snickers and Twix
fat free, too?
I'm forehead hungry.
Yeah, okay.
I'll see you later.
Your forehead
is overweight.
You drive just
like your dad.
I do?
Mm-hmm.
Do you know, this is...
This is where I met your mom
for the first time.
Right there.
She's watching over you
from heaven.
She is?
Mm-hmm.
I think Daddy
has a question for you.
You ready to say grace, kid?
But I don't know what to say.
Oh, it's easy.
Just say whatever is
in your heart.
- You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Come on.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Little Brian's ready
to say grace with us.
- Uh-huh.
- Nice.
Now, hold on.
There's still an empty chair.
He's on the way.
Get rich
Yeah, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay
Moving how I'm speeding
through the fast lane
They say I know magic
how my whips change
They don't see what I see
Go against the game,
you know it's pass me
Zero to hundred,
you know I'm on-on go
Play with my dogs,
Bottles on bottles,
you know I'm on-on go
Moving too fast,
you know we on-on go
I hit the switch and make
the wheels go up
If I got to make the call
You made
the wrong-wrong choice
I roll it up,
you know I'm on-on go
Moving too fast,
Fast lane, bet I push
a hundred in two seconds
I just spent a Bentley
and a Lambo on two necklaces
Take 'em on a high speed,
I'm too reckless
Demon time when I'm in that
Demon, they can't catch it
Bet they get the message,
I'm the best of the bestest
And I'm still waiting
for a bitch to check it
Who want the smoke?
Better hope you don't choke
I be riding two-seater,
itjust me and the scope
I like my gangster
with a mouth full of golds, uh
He hit the lotto, that's goals
Moving how I'm speeding
through the fast lane
They say I know magic
how my whips change
They don't see what I see
Go against the game,
you know it's pass me
Zero to hundred,
you know I'm on-on go
Play with my dogs,
Bottles on bottles,
you know I'm on-on go
Moving too fast,
you know we on-on go
High speed, the cars and me,
you know mine cost ten of 'em
All the scammers calling me
with cars, I need ten of them
Have these... flexing
with these cars
Knowing they rented them
I could put some rappers
all on blast
But ain't gon' mention them
I hit the switch and make
the wheels go up
If I got to make the call
You made
the wrong-wrong choice
I roll it up,
you know I'm on-on go
Moving too fast,
Thank you.
Please.
I tell you where the drive is,
the plans we stole.
I tell you
where it is.
You mean this drive?
These plans?
But you already got it.
Yes, mate.
How else do you think
I stay in this good a shape?
Don't go anywhere.
I'm a lane switcher
Big tank, bank filler
Real killer, die for my
gang member
Gun driller,
dope man dope dealer
Gorilla, bang, bang,
lane switcher
Foot on the gas,
yeah, I'm lane switching
I could not show them
where I'm at
'Cause they stay snitching
I get my killer
the green light
Yeah, I okay the killings
I take the corner,
window down
You see the chain swinging
400,000 on a jet,
200,000 on my left
Richard Mille on my wrist
and it's icy with baguettes
Look, it's me,
Rocky and Skep
Niggas better put respect
on my name
Nigga reach for my chain,
let it bang
I'm a lane switcher
Big tank, bank filler
Real killer, die for my
gang member
Gun driller,
dope man dope dealer
Gorilla, bang, bang,
lane switcher
I know you sicker
than "Sicka"
When you see the big picture
Lane switcher,
put your sister in a twister
paint dripper, drink sipper
Cap peeler, blaow,
make you back Flippa
Ain't no man in the middle
Hit the gas on this V-12,
it's sounding like a gorilla
Drinking like
I hate my liver
Smoking these niggas
like Swishers
I'm just a product
of Memphis
Run up a sack and I flip it
She wanna get
with this pimpin'
But it ain't that simple
I'm a lane switcher
Big tank, bank filler
Real killer, die for my
gang member
Gun driller,
dope man dope dealer
Gorilla, bang, bang,
lane switcher.
I got that heat,
coming in hard
Pull out the flame,
ready to spark
Turn up the beat,
tear it apart
Tear off the leash,
I'm in the yard
I hit 'em hard, I hit 'em hard
Ready to eat,
never gon' starve
Run with the beasts,
swim with the sharks
I'm-a get mine,
put it on God
Ice like the cross,
now who the boss?
Lamborghini with
a hundred in it
Ride on 'em
in the drop Bentley
Get the money
on a money mission
Had to focus,
keep a tunnel vision
No mercy, I'm not even
playing with 'em
Knock 'em off,
I had my man hit 'em
I made me some bands
with 'em
My diamond, they like to go
dance with 'em
No talking 'boutjogging,
we running the city
Opposition now
under submission
You moving your tongue like
you're coming against me
You hurt, in your feelings,
convertible ceilings
One push of a button,
you coming up missing
Count it up, tuck it,
take nothing offensive
Touching them M's,
what I love turned against me
Left me no choice but the
run it up issue
I hit 'em hard, I hit 'em hard
Ready to eat,
never gon' starve
Run with the beasts,
swim with the sharks
I'm-a get mine,
put it on God
Ice like the cross,
now who the boss?
I hit 'em hard, I hit 'em hard
I got that heat,
coming in hard
Pull out the flame,
ready to spark
Turn up the beat,
tear it apart
Tear off the leash,
I'm in the yard, I hit 'em hard
I'm in the dark,
diamond they dancing
They hitting real hard
In the push start
Running my engine in the
back of the car
I took off the chip
and I'm pushing my limits
I'm going real fast,
I'm going real far
I told her don't...
with the bosses and business
I stay in my bag,
I know I'm a star
I stay with them
crash dummies
We don't give a...
we hitting 'em hard
And I'm using my brain 100%,
I don't need a charge
Used to play on the
handlebars
Now we handling firearms
Just lend me the gas and
I'll do the dash
I'll puff, puff and pass,
can't think 'bout the past
I hit 'em hard